(function(){var e={3325:function(e){e.exports=[{submission_id:4664,age:51,comments:"thanks",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:451527,experiment_end_time:1672169690783,experiment_start_time:1672169239256,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:97448,settingName:"books",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:'"Sorry, I don\'t have them at the moment, though I do have books of French love letters if you are interested"',response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4657,age:62,comments:"Nothing to add.",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:307308,experiment_end_time:1672168785168,experiment_start_time:1672168477860,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:47628,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-videoEntertainment",answer:"Afraid not, but i've prepared some movies and games for us all.",response_option:"movie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Netflix?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Netflix.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Netflix",competitor:"some movies",sameCategory:"Xbox games",otherCategory:"Monopoly",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4625,age:40,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:106425,experiment_end_time:1672165773127,experiment_start_time:1672165666702,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:21573,settingName:"interior",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-green",answer:"ah sorry I don't but I have an agave plant you could have?",response_option:"agave",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera plant",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory:"tulips",otherCategory:"an oil painting",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4745,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:1448945,experiment_end_time:1672241577263,experiment_start_time:1672240128318,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:1076593,settingName:"bar",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"Apologies we don't have Sauvignon Blanc but if you like a glass of white wine we have Chardonnay in our bar.",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4678,age:51,comments:"all great.",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:366214,experiment_end_time:1672171954080,experiment_start_time:1672171587866,gender:"female",languages:"English, Estonian",responseTime:74800,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-reptiles",answer:"chameleon is probably near to iguanas, let's go and have a look.",response_option:"iguana",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the chameleon?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, they don't have chameleons here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a chameleon",competitor:"iguanas",sameCategory:"turtles",otherCategory:"a lion",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4652,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:217810,experiment_end_time:1672168701395,experiment_start_time:1672168483585,gender:"female",languages:"english, welsh",responseTime:31522,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-reptiles",answer:"do you mean iguanas?",response_option:"iguana",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the chameleon?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, they don't have chameleons here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a chameleon",competitor:"iguanas",sameCategory:"turtles",otherCategory:"a lion",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4620,age:28,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:231683,experiment_end_time:1672164906357,experiment_start_time:1672164674674,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:64373,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"Hello, unfortunately we don’t have any hamsters but we do have gerbils, would you like to have a look?",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4678,age:51,comments:"all great.",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:366214,experiment_end_time:1672171954080,experiment_start_time:1672171587866,gender:"female",languages:"English, Estonian",responseTime:74683,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-muscle",answer:"hello, we do have kayaks if you are interested.",response_option:"kayak",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent canoes?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent canoes.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"canoes",competitor:"kayaks",sameCategory:"pedal boats",otherCategory:"water ski equipment",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4678,age:51,comments:"all great.",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:366214,experiment_end_time:1672171954080,experiment_start_time:1672171587866,gender:"female",languages:"English, Estonian",responseTime:44816,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"hello, we do offer kickboxing classes, are you interested about it?",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4630,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:158740,experiment_end_time:1672165844403,experiment_start_time:1672165685663,gender:"female",languages:"NA",responseTime:20813,settingName:"books",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"Hmm, not exactly but I have French love letters, would that be any good?",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4667,age:34,comments:"thanks",correct_response:"main",education:"Did not graduate High-school",experiment_duration:150388,experiment_end_time:1672171729239,experiment_start_time:1672171578851,gender:"female",languages:"english",responseTime:29850,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"I  could offer you raspberry pie instead?",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4648,age:31,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:175066,experiment_end_time:1672168658394,experiment_start_time:1672168483328,gender:"male",languages:"English, Polish",responseTime:27949,settingName:"bar",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"I am afraid we do not have iced tea. We do have iced coffee.",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4761,age:41,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:284164,experiment_end_time:1672244039324,experiment_start_time:1672243755160,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:28676,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"I do have a macbook.",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4717,age:55,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:197577,experiment_end_time:1672240332052,experiment_start_time:1672240134475,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:42076,settingName:"interior",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-green",answer:"I do not have an aloe vera plant right now, but I do have an agave plant. Would you be interested in that instead?",response_option:"agave",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera plant",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory:"tulips",otherCategory:"an oil painting",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4667,age:34,comments:"thanks",correct_response:"main",education:"Did not graduate High-school",experiment_duration:150388,experiment_end_time:1672171729239,experiment_start_time:1672171578851,gender:"female",languages:"english",responseTime:38993,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-boardGames",answer:"I don't but we do have monopoly, would that be ok instead?",response_option:"Monopoly",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Scrabble?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Scrabble.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Scrabble",competitor:"Monopoly",sameCategory:"checkers",otherCategory:"some movies",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4636,age:34,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:327744,experiment_end_time:1672165996743,experiment_start_time:1672165668999,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:111712,settingName:"interior",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-green",answer:"I don't have an aloe vera plant right now, I do have an agave plant which looks very similar if you want it.",response_option:"agave",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera plant",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory:"tulips",otherCategory:"an oil painting",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4730,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:280125,experiment_end_time:1672240409731,experiment_start_time:1672240129606,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:48877,settingName:"interior",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"I don't have anyy water colour paintings, but I do have an oil painting if you'd like to see it?",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4661,age:70,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:355447,experiment_end_time:1672168857407,experiment_start_time:1672168501960,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:52104,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-reptiles",answer:"I don’t think they have chameleons but we can have a look at the iguanas.",response_option:"iguana",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the chameleon?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, they don't have chameleons here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a chameleon",competitor:"iguanas",sameCategory:"turtles",otherCategory:"a lion",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4704,age:51,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:239915,experiment_end_time:1672238949713,experiment_start_time:1672238709798,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:69952,settingName:"books",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"I don't think we have books on love poems, but we do have books of French love letters.",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4677,age:33,comments:"an actual enjoyable survey. thanks! :)",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:332258,experiment_end_time:1672171893603,experiment_start_time:1672171561345,gender:"other",languages:"English",responseTime:26030,settingName:"interior",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"I don't, but I do have an oil painting.",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4699,age:58,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:369913,experiment_end_time:1672237275084,experiment_start_time:1672236905171,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:81888,settingName:"interior",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"I dont but would let you have a very nice oil painting now or perhaps paint you a watercolour in the next few weeks.",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4654,age:53,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:262809,experiment_end_time:1672168750445,experiment_start_time:1672168487636,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:94978,settingName:"interior",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"I have a lovely oil painting if you want it.",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4611,age:22,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:108851,experiment_end_time:1672164802989,experiment_start_time:1672164694138,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:28643,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-videoEntertainment",answer:"I have some movies we could watch, but they aren't on Netflix.",response_option:"movie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Netflix?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Netflix.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Netflix",competitor:"some movies",sameCategory:"Xbox games",otherCategory:"Monopoly",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4737,age:69,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:415692,experiment_end_time:1672240553259,experiment_start_time:1672240137567,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:100690,settingName:"books",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-fantasy",answer:"I have some mystery novels which I think you will love.",response_option:"mystery",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you sell psychological thrillers?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t sell psychological thrillers.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"psychological thrillers",competitor:"mystery novels",sameCategory:"adventure novels",otherCategory:"books of French love letters",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4617,age:24,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:183518,experiment_end_time:1672164871173,experiment_start_time:1672164687655,gender:"female",languages:"English, Japanese",responseTime:34546,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-videoEntertainment",answer:"I haven't got Netflix but I've got some movies we could watch. Take a look and pick out something you like!",response_option:"movie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Netflix?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Netflix.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Netflix",competitor:"some movies",sameCategory:"Xbox games",otherCategory:"Monopoly",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4743,age:55,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:670232,experiment_end_time:1672240799995,experiment_start_time:1672240129763,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:130194,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-dogs",answer:"I'm afraid not but we do have the cutest golden retriever that is looking for a loving home would you like to meet him?",response_option:"golden retriever",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any Dalmatians?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any dalmatians.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"dalmatians",competitor:"golden retrievers",sameCategory:"chihuahuas",otherCategory:"gerbils",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4625,age:40,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:106425,experiment_end_time:1672165773127,experiment_start_time:1672165666702,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:19911,settingName:"clothing",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"clothing-clothes",answer:"I'm afraid we don't but we do have other shorts.",response_option:"shorts",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a small designer clothing store. The store currently has the following items in stock:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer comes in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have any Hawaiian shirts?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any Hawaiian shirts.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Hawaiian shirts",competitor:"shorts",sameCategory:"sweatshirts",otherCategory:"necklaces",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4656,age:62,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:305912,experiment_end_time:1672168784565,experiment_start_time:1672168478653,gender:"female",languages:"english",responseTime:67440,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-xl",answer:"I'm not sure that there is a tiger in this zoo. But there is definitely a lion that we can go to see",response_option:"lion",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the tiger?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, they don’t have a tiger here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a tiger",competitor:"a lion",sameCategory:"a giraffe",otherCategory:"iguanas",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4679,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:371599,experiment_end_time:1672171954719,experiment_start_time:1672171583120,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:88536,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-yoga",answer:"I'm really sorry, we don't currently offer yoga, what will do is mention it to our manager as other people have also asked about yoga. In the meantime would you like to try a free plates session?",response_option:"pilates",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer yoga classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have yoga.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"yoga classes",competitor:"a pilates class",sameCategory:"zumba classes",otherCategory:"kickboxing",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4710,age:47,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:159101,experiment_end_time:1672240286434,experiment_start_time:1672240127333,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:34187,settingName:"bar",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"I'm so sorry we don't serve iced tea. I can recommend our iced coffee though.",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4661,age:70,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:355447,experiment_end_time:1672168857407,experiment_start_time:1672168501960,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:50799,settingName:"clothing",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"clothing-acc",answer:"I’m sorry but we do not stock earrings but have a wide choice of necklaces.",response_option:"necklace",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a small designer clothing store. The store currently has the following items in stock:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer comes in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have any earrings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any earrings.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"earrings",competitor:"necklaces",sameCategory:"sunglasses",otherCategory:"shorts",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4624,age:22,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:111973,experiment_end_time:1672165025747,experiment_start_time:1672164913774,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:26446,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-reptiles",answer:"I'm sorry honey, there are no chameleons! Would you like to see an iguana instead?",response_option:"iguana",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the chameleon?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, they don't have chameleons here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a chameleon",competitor:"iguanas",sameCategory:"turtles",otherCategory:"a lion",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4727,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:186614,experiment_end_time:1672240399192,experiment_start_time:1672240212578,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:35744,settingName:"interior",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"I'm sorry I don't, but i do have an oil painting",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4680,age:56,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:408270,experiment_end_time:1672171995137,experiment_start_time:1672171586867,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:31384,settingName:"clothing",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"clothing-acc",answer:"I’m sorry I havnt but I do have some necklaces if your interested",response_option:"necklace",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a small designer clothing store. The store currently has the following items in stock:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer comes in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have any earrings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any earrings.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"earrings",competitor:"necklaces",sameCategory:"sunglasses",otherCategory:"shorts",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4682,age:56,comments:"Thank you",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:534728,experiment_end_time:1672172136788,experiment_start_time:1672171602060,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:94080,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"I’m sorry we don’t at the moment but, we do have gerbils. They’re similar but easier to look after.",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4741,age:63,comments:"All worked fine",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:462786,experiment_end_time:1672240717892,experiment_start_time:1672240255106,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:108372,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-yoga",answer:"I'm sorry we don't offer Yoga currently, but our pilates classes are very popular as it is seen as the next big thing. Are you interested in the social or technical aspects?",response_option:"pilates",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer yoga classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have yoga.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"yoga classes",competitor:"a pilates class",sameCategory:"zumba classes",otherCategory:"kickboxing",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4613,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:112591,experiment_end_time:1672164823439,experiment_start_time:1672164710848,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:22371,settingName:"bar",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"I'm sorry we don't, but we do have iced coffee if that's any good for you?",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4727,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:186614,experiment_end_time:1672240399192,experiment_start_time:1672240212578,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:39119,settingName:"clothing",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"clothing-acc",answer:"I'm sorry we don't, we do have necklaces though if you're interested?",response_option:"necklace",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a small designer clothing store. The store currently has the following items in stock:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer comes in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have any earrings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any earrings.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"earrings",competitor:"necklaces",sameCategory:"sunglasses",otherCategory:"shorts",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4752,age:54,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:196276,experiment_end_time:1672243936719,experiment_start_time:1672243740443,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:34584,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"I'm sorry, no, we don't have any at the moment. Would you consider a gerbil?",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4752,age:54,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:196276,experiment_end_time:1672243936719,experiment_start_time:1672243740443,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:30548,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-console",answer:"I'm sorry, no, we don't have one in stock at the moment. Are you interested in an Xbox?",response_option:"Xbox",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a PlayStation?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a PlayStation.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a PlayStation",competitor:"an Xbox",sameCategory:"a Gameboy",otherCategory:"a MacBook Air",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4752,age:54,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:196276,experiment_end_time:1672243936719,experiment_start_time:1672243740443,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:25182,settingName:"bar",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"I'm sorry, no, we have iced coffee but no iced tea.",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4726,age:53,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:245193,experiment_end_time:1672240385441,experiment_start_time:1672240140248,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:40515,settingName:"bar",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"I'm sorry, we don't but we serve iced coffee",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4623,age:55,comments:"Just to say good luck",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:312976,experiment_end_time:1672165009891,experiment_start_time:1672164696915,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:29874,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"I'm sorry, we only have kickboxing",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4717,age:55,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:197577,experiment_end_time:1672240332052,experiment_start_time:1672240134475,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:32617,settingName:"bar",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"I’m sorry.  The only wine was have right now is Chardonnay.  Would you like a glass of that?",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4723,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:235583,experiment_end_time:1672240357967,experiment_start_time:1672240122384,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:44331,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-videoEntertainment",answer:"I've got some movies lined up for us to check out",response_option:"movie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Netflix?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Netflix.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Netflix",competitor:"some movies",sameCategory:"Xbox games",otherCategory:"Monopoly",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4623,age:55,comments:"Just to say good luck",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:312976,experiment_end_time:1672165009891,experiment_start_time:1672164696915,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:41312,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pizza",answer:"If you accept cheese pizza is vegetarian, then yes we do",response_option:"cheese",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have veggie pizza?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have veggie pizza today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"veggie pizza",competitor:"cheese pizza",sameCategory:"pepperoni pizza",otherCategory:"raspberry pie",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4649,age:41,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:190399,experiment_end_time:1672168663366,experiment_start_time:1672168472967,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:15345,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-reptiles",answer:"it's an iguana.",response_option:"iguana",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the chameleon?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, they don't have chameleons here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a chameleon",competitor:"iguanas",sameCategory:"turtles",otherCategory:"a lion",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4607,age:60,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:232254,experiment_end_time:1672163527107,experiment_start_time:1672163294853,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:61124,settingName:"interior",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-green",answer:"No but I do have an agarve plant.",response_option:"agave",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera plant",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory:"tulips",otherCategory:"an oil painting",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4727,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:186614,experiment_end_time:1672240399192,experiment_start_time:1672240212578,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:22433,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-videoEntertainment",answer:"No but I do have some movies",response_option:"movie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Netflix?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Netflix.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Netflix",competitor:"some movies",sameCategory:"Xbox games",otherCategory:"Monopoly",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4618,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:195248,experiment_end_time:1672164888791,experiment_start_time:1672164693543,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:36281,settingName:"interior",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-green",answer:"No but I have an agave plant",response_option:"agave",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera plant",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory:"tulips",otherCategory:"an oil painting",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4618,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:195248,experiment_end_time:1672164888791,experiment_start_time:1672164693543,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:28609,settingName:"books",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"No but I have books of French love letters",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4655,age:38,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:281556,experiment_end_time:1672168763309,experiment_start_time:1672168481753,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:42572,settingName:"interior",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-green",answer:"No but I have this agave instead- would you like that?",response_option:"agave",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera plant",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory:"tulips",otherCategory:"an oil painting",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4760,age:46,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:303237,experiment_end_time:1672244035387,experiment_start_time:1672243732150,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:42894,settingName:"bar",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"No but i hVe a fantastic chardonnay",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4760,age:46,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:303237,experiment_end_time:1672244035387,experiment_start_time:1672243732150,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:48708,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-yoga",answer:"No but pilates may interest you",response_option:"pilates",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer yoga classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have yoga.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"yoga classes",competitor:"a pilates class",sameCategory:"zumba classes",otherCategory:"kickboxing",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4753,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:214327,experiment_end_time:1672243942307,experiment_start_time:1672243727980,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:31839,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",answer:"No but there is a circus show happening if you are intrested?",response_option:"circus",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory:"a trade fare",otherCategory:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4700,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:361322,experiment_end_time:1672237280621,experiment_start_time:1672236919299,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:79828,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",answer:"No but there is a circus show?",response_option:"circus",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory:"a trade fare",otherCategory:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4747,age:18,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:104759,experiment_end_time:1672243832867,experiment_start_time:1672243728108,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:17488,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",answer:"no but there is with a hip hop DJ",response_option:"hip hop DJ",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory:"live jazz music",otherCategory:"a circus show",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4718,age:38,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:194962,experiment_end_time:1672240333851,experiment_start_time:1672240138889,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:52845,settingName:"bookingAgency",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bookingAgency-lowClassAccommodation",answer:"No but we do have a cheap bed and breakfast available",response_option:"bed-and-breakfast",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a travel booking agency in a medium-sized tourist town. The following types of accommodation are still available for tomorrow night:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the agent:",question:"Is there a bed in the youth hostel available for tomorrow night?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there are no more beds available in the youth hostel available for tomorrow night.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a bed in the youth hostel",competitor:"a room in a cheap bed-and-breakfast",sameCategory:"a room in a budget hotel",otherCategory:"a suite in a four-star hotel",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4636,age:34,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:327744,experiment_end_time:1672165996743,experiment_start_time:1672165668999,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:31024,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"No but we do have a MacBook Air",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4700,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:361322,experiment_end_time:1672237280621,experiment_start_time:1672236919299,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:54707,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"No but we do have a MacBook Air?",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4645,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:114897,experiment_end_time:1672168586674,experiment_start_time:1672168471777,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:17965,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"No but we do have raspberry pie",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4641,age:49,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Did not graduate High-school",experiment_duration:201162,experiment_end_time:1672166111327,experiment_start_time:1672165910165,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:27774,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"No but we do have raspberry pie",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4645,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:114897,experiment_end_time:1672168586674,experiment_start_time:1672168471777,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:27111,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-motor",answer:"No but we do have water ski equipment",response_option:"water ski equipment",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent jet skis?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent jet skis.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"jet skis",competitor:"water ski equipment",sameCategory:"rubber dinghies",otherCategory:"kayaks",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4619,age:34,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:208664,experiment_end_time:1672164898665,experiment_start_time:1672164690001,gender:"female",languages:"British",responseTime:26526,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",answer:"No but we have a circus performance",response_option:"circus",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory:"a trade fare",otherCategory:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4755,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:219635,experiment_end_time:1672243949575,experiment_start_time:1672243729940,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:49493,settingName:"interior",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-green",answer:"No but we have an agave plant",response_option:"agave",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera plant",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory:"tulips",otherCategory:"an oil painting",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4755,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:219635,experiment_end_time:1672243949575,experiment_start_time:1672243729940,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:35932,settingName:"bar",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"No but we have chardonnay",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4610,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:106785,experiment_end_time:1672164788994,experiment_start_time:1672164682209,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:10279,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"No but we have gerbils",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4633,age:40,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:200187,experiment_end_time:1672165880913,experiment_start_time:1672165680726,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:22212,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"No but we have gerbils if you like",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4747,age:18,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:104759,experiment_end_time:1672243832867,experiment_start_time:1672243728108,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:11946,settingName:"bar",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"no but we have iced coffee",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4651,age:60,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:201156,experiment_end_time:1672168679852,experiment_start_time:1672168478696,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:51312,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"No but we have raspberry pie, would you like that?",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4700,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:361322,experiment_end_time:1672237280621,experiment_start_time:1672236919299,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:73846,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"No but we sell cigarettes?",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4684,age:67,comments:"none",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:431656,experiment_end_time:1672172747943,experiment_start_time:1672172316287,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:61069,settingName:"interior",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-green",answer:"No but would you consider an agave?",response_option:"agave",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera plant",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory:"tulips",otherCategory:"an oil painting",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4633,age:40,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:200187,experiment_end_time:1672165880913,experiment_start_time:1672165680726,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:24868,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"No but you could try kick-boxing if you like",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4642,age:68,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Did not graduate High-school",experiment_duration:506044,experiment_end_time:1672166176808,experiment_start_time:1672165670764,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:133815,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-videoEntertainment",answer:"No do not have Netflix But have some movies we can watch.",response_option:"movie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Netflix?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Netflix.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Netflix",competitor:"some movies",sameCategory:"Xbox games",otherCategory:"Monopoly",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4681,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:245085,experiment_end_time:1672172087584,experiment_start_time:1672171842499,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:107781,settingName:"interior",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"No I don't, but I do have an oil painting",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4666,age:25,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:114802,experiment_end_time:1672171693907,experiment_start_time:1672171579105,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:19320,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-videoEntertainment",answer:"No I don't, but I have lots of movies at hand here",response_option:"movie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Netflix?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Netflix.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Netflix",competitor:"some movies",sameCategory:"Xbox games",otherCategory:"Monopoly",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4761,age:41,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:284164,experiment_end_time:1672244039324,experiment_start_time:1672243755160,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:39285,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-boardGames",answer:"No I don't, but I have monopoly.",response_option:"Monopoly",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Scrabble?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Scrabble.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Scrabble",competitor:"Monopoly",sameCategory:"checkers",otherCategory:"some movies",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4645,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:114897,experiment_end_time:1672168586674,experiment_start_time:1672168471777,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:25916,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"No I only have a macnook air",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4632,age:69,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:208141,experiment_end_time:1672165879722,experiment_start_time:1672165671581,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:29856,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-dogs",answer:"No I'm sorry, but we have some lovely golden retrievers if you were interested",response_option:"golden retriever",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any Dalmatians?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any dalmatians.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"dalmatians",competitor:"golden retrievers",sameCategory:"chihuahuas",otherCategory:"gerbils",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4743,age:55,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:670232,experiment_end_time:1672240799995,experiment_start_time:1672240129763,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:148381,settingName:"bar",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"No madam but I have a delicious Chardonnay that would brighten anyone's day , would you care to sample some?",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4731,age:51,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:312396,experiment_end_time:1672240431558,experiment_start_time:1672240119162,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:27672,settingName:"bar",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"No not today.  May I interest you in an iced coffee?",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4645,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:114897,experiment_end_time:1672168586674,experiment_start_time:1672168471777,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:14229,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"No only cigarettes",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4615,age:21,comments:"I think just make the  font size a little bit bigger",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:164587,experiment_end_time:1672164847535,experiment_start_time:1672164682948,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:15526,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"No only the Macbook air.",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4668,age:31,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:162355,experiment_end_time:1672171740950,experiment_start_time:1672171578595,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:18157,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-console",answer:"No playstations sorry, we do have an Xbox which is similar",response_option:"Xbox",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a PlayStation?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a PlayStation.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a PlayStation",competitor:"an Xbox",sameCategory:"a Gameboy",otherCategory:"a MacBook Air",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4640,age:62,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:444611,experiment_end_time:1672166112109,experiment_start_time:1672165667498,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:84674,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-muscle",answer:"No sir but we do rent the same family of boats, our version is the kayak",response_option:"kayak",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent canoes?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent canoes.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"canoes",competitor:"kayaks",sameCategory:"pedal boats",otherCategory:"water ski equipment",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4607,age:60,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:232254,experiment_end_time:1672163527107,experiment_start_time:1672163294853,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:30326,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-yoga",answer:"No sorry but we can offer pilates.",response_option:"pilates",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer yoga classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have yoga.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"yoga classes",competitor:"a pilates class",sameCategory:"zumba classes",otherCategory:"kickboxing",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4753,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:214327,experiment_end_time:1672243942307,experiment_start_time:1672243727980,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:62825,settingName:"bookingAgency",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bookingAgency-lowClassAccommodation",answer:"No sorry but we have availibility at a budget hotel?",response_option:"budget hotel",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a travel booking agency in a medium-sized tourist town. The following types of accommodation are still available for tomorrow night:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the agent:",question:"Is there a bed in the youth hostel available for tomorrow night?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there are no more beds available in the youth hostel available for tomorrow night.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a bed in the youth hostel",competitor:"a room in a cheap bed-and-breakfast",sameCategory:"a room in a budget hotel",otherCategory:"a suite in a four-star hotel",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4753,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:214327,experiment_end_time:1672243942307,experiment_start_time:1672243727980,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:37357,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-dogs",answer:"No sorry but we have golden retrievers if you would like to take a look?",response_option:"golden retriever",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any Dalmatians?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any dalmatians.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"dalmatians",competitor:"golden retrievers",sameCategory:"chihuahuas",otherCategory:"gerbils",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4675,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:292624,experiment_end_time:1672171866639,experiment_start_time:1672171574015,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:25668,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"No sorry we only have raspberry pie available.",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4722,age:76,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:221967,experiment_end_time:1672240350422,experiment_start_time:1672240128455,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:39638,settingName:"bar",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"No sorry, But the Chardonnay is very good",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4616,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:132469,experiment_end_time:1672164859766,experiment_start_time:1672164727297,gender:"female",languages:"NA",responseTime:25738,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"No sorry, we have the MacBook Air though if that interests you.",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4693,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:195676,experiment_end_time:1672237105338,experiment_start_time:1672236909662,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:31896,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"No sorry. I do have some cigarettes if you are interested in those instead?",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4688,age:34,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:143033,experiment_end_time:1672237050935,experiment_start_time:1672236907902,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:37264,settingName:"bookingAgency",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bookingAgency-highClassAccommodation",answer:"No there isn't, sorry, but there is a suite in a four star hotel.",response_option:"four-star hotel",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a travel booking agency in a medium-sized tourist town. The following types of accommodation are still available for tomorrow night:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAn older man walks in and asks the agent:",question:"Is a single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a single room in a five-star hotel",competitor:"a suite in a four-star hotel",sameCategory:"an expensive apartment close to the city",otherCategory:"a room in a cheap bed-and-breakfast",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4719,age:34,comments:"Nil",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:212503,experiment_end_time:1672240338178,experiment_start_time:1672240125675,gender:"female",languages:"english",responseTime:32777,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pizza",answer:"No we don't but you might like to try the cheese pizza?",response_option:"cheese",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have veggie pizza?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have veggie pizza today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"veggie pizza",competitor:"cheese pizza",sameCategory:"pepperoni pizza",otherCategory:"raspberry pie",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4725,age:40,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:249426,experiment_end_time:1672240369811,experiment_start_time:1672240120385,gender:"female",languages:"english",responseTime:76706,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-muscle",answer:"No we don't have canoes but we do have kayaks which are pretty similar although they are closed boat and have a slightly different padle",response_option:"kayak",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent canoes?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent canoes.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"canoes",competitor:"kayaks",sameCategory:"pedal boats",otherCategory:"water ski equipment",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4681,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:245085,experiment_end_time:1672172087584,experiment_start_time:1672171842499,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:39435,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-console",answer:"No we don't sorry, we do have an xbox though, would this be ok?",response_option:"Xbox",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a PlayStation?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a PlayStation.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a PlayStation",competitor:"an Xbox",sameCategory:"a Gameboy",otherCategory:"a MacBook Air",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4712,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:175776,experiment_end_time:1672240302383,experiment_start_time:1672240126607,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:25459,settingName:"bar",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"No we have iced coffee though.",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4712,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:175776,experiment_end_time:1672240302383,experiment_start_time:1672240126607,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:29509,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"No we have kickboxing classes only.",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4642,age:68,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Did not graduate High-school",experiment_duration:506044,experiment_end_time:1672166176808,experiment_start_time:1672165670764,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:92832,settingName:"interior",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"No, but have a oil painting you can look at.",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4708,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:145436,experiment_end_time:1672240271362,experiment_start_time:1672240125926,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:28576,settingName:"bookingAgency",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bookingAgency-highClassAccommodation",answer:"No, but how about a suite in a four star hotel?",response_option:"four-star hotel",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a travel booking agency in a medium-sized tourist town. The following types of accommodation are still available for tomorrow night:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAn older man walks in and asks the agent:",question:"Is a single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a single room in a five-star hotel",competitor:"a suite in a four-star hotel",sameCategory:"an expensive apartment close to the city",otherCategory:"a room in a cheap bed-and-breakfast",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4650,age:47,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:202445,experiment_end_time:1672168673782,experiment_start_time:1672168471337,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:36170,settingName:"interior",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"No, but I do have an oil painting you could have.",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4630,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:158740,experiment_end_time:1672165844403,experiment_start_time:1672165685663,gender:"female",languages:"NA",responseTime:17245,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-boardGames",answer:"No, but I do have monopoly!",response_option:"Monopoly",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Scrabble?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Scrabble.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Scrabble",competitor:"Monopoly",sameCategory:"checkers",otherCategory:"some movies",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4656,age:62,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:305912,experiment_end_time:1672168784565,experiment_start_time:1672168478653,gender:"female",languages:"english",responseTime:44961,settingName:"books",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"No, but I do have some books of French love letters",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4637,age:56,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:293013,experiment_end_time:1672166014283,experiment_start_time:1672165721270,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:48173,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"No, but i have a macbook air",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4726,age:53,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:245193,experiment_end_time:1672240385441,experiment_start_time:1672240140248,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:35490,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-videoEntertainment",answer:"No, but I have movies lined up for us to choose from.",response_option:"movie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Netflix?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Netflix.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Netflix",competitor:"some movies",sameCategory:"Xbox games",otherCategory:"Monopoly",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4647,age:43,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:120215,experiment_end_time:1672168597056,experiment_start_time:1672168476841,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:18200,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",answer:"No, but there is a circus show.",response_option:"circus",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory:"a trade fare",otherCategory:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4759,age:39,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:268729,experiment_end_time:1672243997648,experiment_start_time:1672243728919,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:74553,settingName:"kidsActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"kidsActivities-sports",answer:"No, but there is an acrobatics class.",response_option:"acrobatics",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a children’s summer camp. Today a new group of children arrived. They need to sign up for different activities. The camp offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA kid walks up to a teacher and asks:",question:"Is there a gymnastics class?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no gymnastics class.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a gymnastics class",competitor:"an acrobatics class",sameCategory:"a karate class",otherCategory:"a watercolor painting class",character_template:"The teacher replies:"},{submission_id:4672,age:33,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"NA",experiment_duration:215988,experiment_end_time:1672171791741,experiment_start_time:1672171575753,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:24269,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-videoEntertainment",answer:"No, but there's a selection of movies if you want to choose one.",response_option:"movie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Netflix?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Netflix.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Netflix",competitor:"some movies",sameCategory:"Xbox games",otherCategory:"Monopoly",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4689,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:173006,experiment_end_time:1672237066240,experiment_start_time:1672236893234,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:25197,settingName:"kidsActivities",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"kidsActivities-sports",answer:"No, but there's acrobatics",response_option:"acrobatics",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a children’s summer camp. Today a new group of children arrived. They need to sign up for different activities. The camp offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA kid walks up to a teacher and asks:",question:"Is there a gymnastics class?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no gymnastics class.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a gymnastics class",competitor:"an acrobatics class",sameCategory:"a karate class",otherCategory:"a watercolor painting class",character_template:"The teacher replies:"},{submission_id:4647,age:43,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:120215,experiment_end_time:1672168597056,experiment_start_time:1672168476841,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:22240,settingName:"kidsActivities",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"kidsActivities-crafts",answer:"No, but there's carpentry if you're interested.",response_option:"carpentry",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a children’s summer camp. Today a new group of children arrived. They need to sign up for different activities. The camp offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA kid walks up to a teacher and asks:",question:"Is there a pottery class?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no pottery class.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a pottery class",competitor:"a watercolor painting class",sameCategory:"a carpentry workshop",otherCategory:"an acrobatics class",character_template:"The teacher replies:"},{submission_id:4751,age:28,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:147153,experiment_end_time:1672243869023,experiment_start_time:1672243721870,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:18605,settingName:"books",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"No, but we do have a book on French love letters.\n",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4614,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:142055,experiment_end_time:1672164834373,experiment_start_time:1672164692318,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:20315,settingName:"books",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"No, but we do have French love letters.",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4685,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:95714,experiment_end_time:1672237002197,experiment_start_time:1672236906483,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:13701,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-sweets",answer:"No, but we do have gingerbread.",response_option:"gingerbread",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cookies?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cookies.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cookies",competitor:"gingerbread",sameCategory:"granola bars",otherCategory:"cigarettes",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4729,age:24,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:264807,experiment_end_time:1672240412648,experiment_start_time:1672240147841,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:33401,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"No, but we do offer kickboxing classes. Would you be interested in signing up for the kickboxing classes?",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4619,age:34,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:208664,experiment_end_time:1672164898665,experiment_start_time:1672164690001,gender:"female",languages:"British",responseTime:50345,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-yoga",answer:"No, but we do offer Pilates",response_option:"pilates",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer yoga classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have yoga.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"yoga classes",competitor:"a pilates class",sameCategory:"zumba classes",otherCategory:"kickboxing",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4750,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:132518,experiment_end_time:1672243858741,experiment_start_time:1672243726223,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:18836,settingName:"books",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"No, but we have books of French love letters!",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4708,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:145436,experiment_end_time:1672240271362,experiment_start_time:1672240125926,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:23376,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"No, but we have gerbils.",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4759,age:39,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:268729,experiment_end_time:1672243997648,experiment_start_time:1672243728919,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:35817,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"No, but we offer kickboxing lessons.",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4647,age:43,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:120215,experiment_end_time:1672168597056,experiment_start_time:1672168476841,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:25696,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"No, but we sell cigarettes.",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4710,age:47,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:159101,experiment_end_time:1672240286434,experiment_start_time:1672240127333,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:21264,settingName:"interior",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"No, how about an oil painting?",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4685,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:95714,experiment_end_time:1672237002197,experiment_start_time:1672236906483,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:11022,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-console",answer:"No, how about an Xbox?",response_option:"Xbox",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a PlayStation?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a PlayStation.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a PlayStation",competitor:"an Xbox",sameCategory:"a Gameboy",otherCategory:"a MacBook Air",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4650,age:47,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:202445,experiment_end_time:1672168673782,experiment_start_time:1672168471337,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:30243,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-videoEntertainment",answer:"No, how about we watch a movie instead?",response_option:"movie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Netflix?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Netflix.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Netflix",competitor:"some movies",sameCategory:"Xbox games",otherCategory:"Monopoly",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4669,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:166429,experiment_end_time:1672171749381,experiment_start_time:1672171582952,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:35646,settingName:"interior",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-green",answer:"No, I have an agave plant",response_option:"agave",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera plant",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory:"tulips",otherCategory:"an oil painting",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4765,age:35,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:205041,experiment_end_time:1672244285138,experiment_start_time:1672244080097,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:76969,settingName:"interior",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"No, i have an oil painting though",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4619,age:34,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:208664,experiment_end_time:1672164898665,experiment_start_time:1672164690001,gender:"female",languages:"British",responseTime:31542,settingName:"bar",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"No, I have chardonnay",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4711,age:38,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:171437,experiment_end_time:1672240296548,experiment_start_time:1672240125111,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:25618,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-boardGames",answer:"No, i have Monopoly though",response_option:"Monopoly",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Scrabble?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Scrabble.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Scrabble",competitor:"Monopoly",sameCategory:"checkers",otherCategory:"some movies",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4672,age:33,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"NA",experiment_duration:215988,experiment_end_time:1672171791741,experiment_start_time:1672171575753,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:46931,settingName:"interior",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"No, I'm sorry but the only painting I have at the moment is an oil painting.",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4632,age:69,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:208141,experiment_end_time:1672165879722,experiment_start_time:1672165671581,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:29952,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"NO, I'm sorry I only have cigarettes.",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4677,age:33,comments:"an actual enjoyable survey. thanks! :)",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:332258,experiment_end_time:1672171893603,experiment_start_time:1672171561345,gender:"other",languages:"English",responseTime:74771,settingName:"bookingAgency",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bookingAgency-highClassAccommodation",answer:"no, I'm sorry, that is not available, but we do have a four star hotel option open.",response_option:"four-star hotel",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a travel booking agency in a medium-sized tourist town. The following types of accommodation are still available for tomorrow night:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAn older man walks in and asks the agent:",question:"Is a single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a single room in a five-star hotel",competitor:"a suite in a four-star hotel",sameCategory:"an expensive apartment close to the city",otherCategory:"a room in a cheap bed-and-breakfast",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4647,age:43,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:120215,experiment_end_time:1672168597056,experiment_start_time:1672168476841,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:16424,settingName:"interior",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-green",answer:"No, only agave plant.",response_option:"agave",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera plant",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory:"tulips",otherCategory:"an oil painting",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4711,age:38,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:171437,experiment_end_time:1672240296548,experiment_start_time:1672240125111,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:28266,settingName:"bar",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"No, our wine choice is Chardonnay",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4657,age:62,comments:"Nothing to add.",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:307308,experiment_end_time:1672168785168,experiment_start_time:1672168477860,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:54506,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"No, sorry, but we do have gerbils if you're open to another type of small pet.",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4702,age:54,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:432511,experiment_end_time:1672237346494,experiment_start_time:1672236913983,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:71306,settingName:"bar",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"No, sorry, we do not, but we do have iced coffee.",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4651,age:60,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:201156,experiment_end_time:1672168679852,experiment_start_time:1672168478696,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:30234,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"No, sorry. Cigarettes though, would you like those instead?",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4655,age:38,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:281556,experiment_end_time:1672168763309,experiment_start_time:1672168481753,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:37165,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-yoga",answer:"No, the closest we offer is Pilates- you should give it a try",response_option:"pilates",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer yoga classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have yoga.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"yoga classes",competitor:"a pilates class",sameCategory:"zumba classes",otherCategory:"kickboxing",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4605,age:23,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:247064,experiment_end_time:1672163430843,experiment_start_time:1672163183779,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:95905,settingName:"bookingAgency",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bookingAgency-highClassAccommodation",answer:"No, there are no single rooms in any five-star hotels available. The closest to this is a suite in a four-star hotel.",response_option:"four-star hotel",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a travel booking agency in a medium-sized tourist town. The following types of accommodation are still available for tomorrow night:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAn older man walks in and asks the agent:",question:"Is a single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a single room in a five-star hotel",competitor:"a suite in a four-star hotel",sameCategory:"an expensive apartment close to the city",otherCategory:"a room in a cheap bed-and-breakfast",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4765,age:35,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:205041,experiment_end_time:1672244285138,experiment_start_time:1672244080097,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:48639,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",answer:"no, there is a hip-hop dj though",response_option:"hip hop DJ",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory:"live jazz music",otherCategory:"a circus show",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4694,age:25,comments:"i enjoyed this id like to do more like this",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:213829,experiment_end_time:1672237113708,experiment_start_time:1672236899879,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:33920,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"no, unfortunatley we only have a Macbook Air in stock at the moment",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4650,age:47,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:202445,experiment_end_time:1672168673782,experiment_start_time:1672168471337,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:33765,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"No, we do kickboxing if that is of interest?",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4683,age:43,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:101490,experiment_end_time:1672172196659,experiment_start_time:1672172095169,gender:"female",languages:"english",responseTime:12035,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"no, we do kickboxing.",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4658,age:63,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:303596,experiment_end_time:1672168787421,experiment_start_time:1672168483825,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:64316,settingName:"interior",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"No, we don't have any watercolour paintings but we do have oil paintings, if you would like to take a look.",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4765,age:35,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:205041,experiment_end_time:1672244285138,experiment_start_time:1672244080097,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:22881,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"No, we have gerbils",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4739,age:38,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:511041,experiment_end_time:1672240637108,experiment_start_time:1672240126067,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:24101,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"No, we have gerbils though which are similar to hamsters.",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4655,age:38,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:281556,experiment_end_time:1672168763309,experiment_start_time:1672168481753,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:34924,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"No, we only have the MacBook Air at the moment.",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4637,age:56,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:293013,experiment_end_time:1672166014283,experiment_start_time:1672165721270,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:41909,settingName:"books",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"No, would french love letters be of any interest?",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4631,age:56,comments:"All good!",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:180499,experiment_end_time:1672165849506,experiment_start_time:1672165669007,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:41232,settingName:"bar",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"No,sorry, but we do have iced coffee, if you’d like that.",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4649,age:41,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:190399,experiment_end_time:1672168663366,experiment_start_time:1672168472967,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:53304,settingName:"interior",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"no. but I have an oil painting",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4649,age:41,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:190399,experiment_end_time:1672168663366,experiment_start_time:1672168472967,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:22039,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"no. but we have gerbils",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4643,age:60,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:678649,experiment_end_time:1672166354788,experiment_start_time:1672165676139,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:148032,settingName:"interior",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"No. I have oil paintings though. Would you like to have a look at them ? I painted them myself.",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4669,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:166429,experiment_end_time:1672171749381,experiment_start_time:1672171582952,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:36004,settingName:"books",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"No. We have a book of french love letters",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4669,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:166429,experiment_end_time:1672171749381,experiment_start_time:1672171582952,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:24381,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"No. We have a MacBook Air",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4737,age:69,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:415692,experiment_end_time:1672240553259,experiment_start_time:1672240137567,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:52095,settingName:"bar",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"No…..but I have some iced coffee which is the best in town….you will love it.",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4737,age:69,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:415692,experiment_end_time:1672240553259,experiment_start_time:1672240137567,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:60232,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"No….but we have some great kickboxing classes that I think you will love.",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4616,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:132469,experiment_end_time:1672164859766,experiment_start_time:1672164727297,gender:"female",languages:"NA",responseTime:21221,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"Not a cake, but we have raspberry pie.",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4722,age:76,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:221967,experiment_end_time:1672240350422,experiment_start_time:1672240128455,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:40644,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",answer:"Not a theatre performance but they will love the Circus which starts shortly",response_option:"circus",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory:"a trade fare",otherCategory:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4640,age:62,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:444611,experiment_end_time:1672166112109,experiment_start_time:1672165667498,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:63969,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",answer:"not today however i can get you into a hip hop session.",response_option:"hip hop DJ",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory:"live jazz music",otherCategory:"a circus show",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4721,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:222618,experiment_end_time:1672240345239,experiment_start_time:1672240122621,gender:"female",languages:"English, French",responseTime:32032,settingName:"interior",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"Not watercolour but I do have an oil painting if that interests you",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4721,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:222618,experiment_end_time:1672240345239,experiment_start_time:1672240122621,gender:"female",languages:"English, French",responseTime:46511,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",answer:"Not with electronic music, but there is a club event with a hip hop DJ",response_option:"hip hop DJ",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory:"live jazz music",otherCategory:"a circus show",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4654,age:53,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:262809,experiment_end_time:1672168750445,experiment_start_time:1672168487636,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:41159,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-muscle",answer:"Oh yes, we have wonderful kayaks",response_option:"kayak",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent canoes?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent canoes.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"canoes",competitor:"kayaks",sameCategory:"pedal boats",otherCategory:"water ski equipment",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4652,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:217810,experiment_end_time:1672168701395,experiment_start_time:1672168483585,gender:"female",languages:"english, welsh",responseTime:35979,settingName:"interior",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-deco",answer:"only oil, want to take a look?",response_option:"oil painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have watercolour paintings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have watercolor paintings.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"watercolor paintings",competitor:"an oil painting",sameCategory:"some printed photographs",otherCategory:"an agave plant",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4670,age:33,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:170482,experiment_end_time:1672171760039,experiment_start_time:1672171589557,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:53733,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pizza",answer:"Our only vegi pizza the cheese pizza",response_option:"cheese",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have veggie pizza?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have veggie pizza today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"veggie pizza",competitor:"cheese pizza",sameCategory:"pepperoni pizza",otherCategory:"raspberry pie",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4756,age:26,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:227328,experiment_end_time:1672243962813,experiment_start_time:1672243735485,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:29308,settingName:"books",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-fantasy",answer:"Sadly not, we do have an excellent selection of mystery novels available though - would that interest you?",response_option:"mystery",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you sell psychological thrillers?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t sell psychological thrillers.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"psychological thrillers",competitor:"mystery novels",sameCategory:"adventure novels",otherCategory:"books of French love letters",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4694,age:25,comments:"i enjoyed this id like to do more like this",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:213829,experiment_end_time:1672237113708,experiment_start_time:1672236899879,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:35903,settingName:"bar",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"sadly we have no sauvignon blanc in at the moment but we do offer a lovely chardonnay",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4757,age:57,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:233601,experiment_end_time:1672243964113,experiment_start_time:1672243730512,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:36709,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-xl",answer:"Shall we go and look at the lion? That’s the closest thing to a tiger they have here today.",response_option:"lion",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the tiger?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, they don’t have a tiger here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a tiger",competitor:"a lion",sameCategory:"a giraffe",otherCategory:"iguanas",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4762,age:66,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:393355,experiment_end_time:1672244129375,experiment_start_time:1672243736020,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:98638,settingName:"books",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-fantasy",answer:"Sorry no but I do have some mystery novels if they would be any good",response_option:"mystery",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you sell psychological thrillers?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t sell psychological thrillers.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"psychological thrillers",competitor:"mystery novels",sameCategory:"adventure novels",otherCategory:"books of French love letters",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4697,age:57,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:291393,experiment_end_time:1672237238869,experiment_start_time:1672236947476,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:34658,settingName:"bar",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"Sorry no iced tea, but our iced coffee is really popular",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4745,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:1448945,experiment_end_time:1672241577263,experiment_start_time:1672240128318,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:88773,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",answer:"Sorry no theater performance for children today. There is a circus show if you are interested",response_option:"circus",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory:"a trade fare",otherCategory:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4736,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:420516,experiment_end_time:1672240544516,experiment_start_time:1672240124e3,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:60201,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"Sorry no, we don't. we only have a MacBook Air",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4634,age:69,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Did not graduate High-school",experiment_duration:227212,experiment_end_time:1672165893433,experiment_start_time:1672165666221,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:38591,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-dogs",answer:"Sorry the only dog we have available is golden retrievers",response_option:"golden retriever",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any Dalmatians?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any dalmatians.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"dalmatians",competitor:"golden retrievers",sameCategory:"chihuahuas",otherCategory:"gerbils",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4699,age:58,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:369913,experiment_end_time:1672237275084,experiment_start_time:1672236905171,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:62735,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-muscle",answer:"Sorry we dont but i can offer you a kayak which is very similar.",response_option:"kayak",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent canoes?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent canoes.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"canoes",competitor:"kayaks",sameCategory:"pedal boats",otherCategory:"water ski equipment",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4627,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:169632,experiment_end_time:1672165773559,experiment_start_time:1672165603927,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:30770,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"Sorry we only offer kickboxing",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4632,age:69,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:208141,experiment_end_time:1672165879722,experiment_start_time:1672165671581,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:49439,settingName:"bar",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"Sorry, but no.  However ,we do have some rather delicious chardonnay",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4692,age:20,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:194401,experiment_end_time:1672237099998,experiment_start_time:1672236905597,gender:"other",languages:"English",responseTime:41057,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-reptiles",answer:"Sorry, I don't think there are any chameleons! We can go to the igaunas if you want instead?",response_option:"iguana",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the chameleon?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, they don't have chameleons here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a chameleon",competitor:"iguanas",sameCategory:"turtles",otherCategory:"a lion",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4728,age:46,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:272615,experiment_end_time:1672240412216,experiment_start_time:1672240139601,gender:"female",languages:"english",responseTime:39195,settingName:"bar",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"sorry, just iced coffee, would you like some water?",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4724,age:43,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:238749,experiment_end_time:1672240365099,experiment_start_time:1672240126350,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:34823,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pizza",answer:"Sorry, no veggie pizza today but there is cheese pizza.",response_option:"cheese",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have veggie pizza?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have veggie pizza today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"veggie pizza",competitor:"cheese pizza",sameCategory:"pepperoni pizza",otherCategory:"raspberry pie",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4652,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:217810,experiment_end_time:1672168701395,experiment_start_time:1672168483585,gender:"female",languages:"english, welsh",responseTime:70989,settingName:"clothing",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"clothing-acc",answer:"sorry, unfortunately we're out of stock at this time. Would you be interested in necklaces instead perhaps?",response_option:"necklace",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a small designer clothing store. The store currently has the following items in stock:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer comes in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have any earrings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any earrings.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"earrings",competitor:"necklaces",sameCategory:"sunglasses",otherCategory:"shorts",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4735,age:42,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:389836,experiment_end_time:1672240523325,experiment_start_time:1672240133489,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:25187,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"Sorry, we do not offer boxing classes. We do, however offer kickboxing classes.",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4724,age:43,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:238749,experiment_end_time:1672240365099,experiment_start_time:1672240126350,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:44089,settingName:"bar",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"Sorry, we don’t have iced tea, but we do serve a refreshing iced coffee.",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4741,age:63,comments:"All worked fine",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:462786,experiment_end_time:1672240717892,experiment_start_time:1672240255106,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:50083,settingName:"friendsActivities",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"friendsActivities-boardGames",answer:"Sure we have scrabble. Lets see who prefers to to Monopoly.",response_option:"Monopoly",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at a friend’s house. For activities, the friend prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend asks the host:",question:"Do you have Scrabble?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Scrabble.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Scrabble",competitor:"Monopoly",sameCategory:"checkers",otherCategory:"some movies",character_template:"The host replies:"},{submission_id:4697,age:57,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:291393,experiment_end_time:1672237238869,experiment_start_time:1672236947476,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:49641,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-reptiles",answer:"The chameleon is hiding, let's go and see if he is in with the iguanas",response_option:"iguana",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the chameleon?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, they don't have chameleons here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a chameleon",competitor:"iguanas",sameCategory:"turtles",otherCategory:"a lion",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4762,age:66,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:393355,experiment_end_time:1672244129375,experiment_start_time:1672243736020,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:52171,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pizza",answer:"the only pizza I have is a cheese pizza if that would do",response_option:"cheese",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have veggie pizza?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have veggie pizza today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"veggie pizza",competitor:"cheese pizza",sameCategory:"pepperoni pizza",otherCategory:"raspberry pie",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4607,age:60,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:232254,experiment_end_time:1672163527107,experiment_start_time:1672163294853,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:38855,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-xl",answer:"There aren't any tigers but we could see a lion.",response_option:"lion",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the tiger?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, they don’t have a tiger here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a tiger",competitor:"a lion",sameCategory:"a giraffe",otherCategory:"iguanas",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4706,age:23,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:119359,experiment_end_time:1672240253405,experiment_start_time:1672240134046,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:24917,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",answer:"there is a circus",response_option:"circus",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory:"a trade fare",otherCategory:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4628,age:25,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:150375,experiment_end_time:1672165832167,experiment_start_time:1672165681792,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:20435,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",answer:"There is a circus show",response_option:"circus",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory:"a trade fare",otherCategory:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4695,age:41,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:250508,experiment_end_time:1672237158920,experiment_start_time:1672236908412,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:38836,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",answer:"There is a circus show today which is suitable for children, but no theatre I'm afraid.",response_option:"circus",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory:"a trade fare",otherCategory:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4731,age:51,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:312396,experiment_end_time:1672240431558,experiment_start_time:1672240119162,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:62137,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",answer:"There is a club event but it is playing hip hop music should this be of interest to you.",response_option:"hip hop DJ",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory:"live jazz music",otherCategory:"a circus show",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4756,age:26,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:227328,experiment_end_time:1672243962813,experiment_start_time:1672243735485,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:48530,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",answer:"There is a club event today with a hip hop DJ, not electronic music I'm afraid.",response_option:"hip hop DJ",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory:"live jazz music",otherCategory:"a circus show",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4759,age:39,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:268729,experiment_end_time:1672243997648,experiment_start_time:1672243728919,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:40245,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",answer:"There is a club event with a hip hop DJ.",response_option:"hip hop DJ",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory:"live jazz music",otherCategory:"a circus show",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4613,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:112591,experiment_end_time:1672164823439,experiment_start_time:1672164710848,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:26191,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",answer:"There is a club event, but it's with hip hop rather than electronic music.",response_option:"hip hop DJ",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory:"live jazz music",otherCategory:"a circus show",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4703,age:44,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:896341,experiment_end_time:1672237798872,experiment_start_time:1672236902531,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:52680,settingName:"kidsActivities",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"kidsActivities-sports",answer:"There is an acrobatics class which is similar to activities you would do in a gymnastics class.",response_option:"acrobatics",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a children’s summer camp. Today a new group of children arrived. They need to sign up for different activities. The camp offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA kid walks up to a teacher and asks:",question:"Is there a gymnastics class?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no gymnastics class.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a gymnastics class",competitor:"an acrobatics class",sameCategory:"a karate class",otherCategory:"a watercolor painting class",character_template:"The teacher replies:"},{submission_id:4665,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:92698,experiment_end_time:1672171677659,experiment_start_time:1672171584961,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:22740,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",answer:"There is no club event with electronic music today, only hip hop",response_option:"hip hop DJ",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory:"live jazz music",otherCategory:"a circus show",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4748,age:24,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:106734,experiment_end_time:1672243838314,experiment_start_time:1672243731580,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:26761,settingName:"kidsActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"kidsActivities-crafts",answer:"There isn't but I bet you would love the painting class!",response_option:"watercolor painting",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a children’s summer camp. Today a new group of children arrived. They need to sign up for different activities. The camp offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA kid walks up to a teacher and asks:",question:"Is there a pottery class?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no pottery class.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a pottery class",competitor:"a watercolor painting class",sameCategory:"a carpentry workshop",otherCategory:"an acrobatics class",character_template:"The teacher replies:"},{submission_id:4673,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:210370,experiment_end_time:1672171793507,experiment_start_time:1672171583137,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:29152,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",answer:"There isn’t today, although there is a circus show. Would this be of interest to you?",response_option:"circus",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory:"a trade fare",otherCategory:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4689,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:173006,experiment_end_time:1672237066240,experiment_start_time:1672236893234,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:56033,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-reptiles",answer:"There's no chameleons, let's see iguanas instead",response_option:"iguana",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the chameleon?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, they don't have chameleons here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a chameleon",competitor:"iguanas",sameCategory:"turtles",otherCategory:"a lion",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4635,age:39,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:294443,experiment_end_time:1672165986021,experiment_start_time:1672165691578,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:45099,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-xl",answer:"They don't have a tiger, but we can go see the lion.",response_option:"lion",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the tiger?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, they don’t have a tiger here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a tiger",competitor:"a lion",sameCategory:"a giraffe",otherCategory:"iguanas",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4668,age:31,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:162355,experiment_end_time:1672171740950,experiment_start_time:1672171578595,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:34900,settingName:"kidsActivities",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"kidsActivities-sports",answer:"Unfortuantely not, however we have acrobatics, which is similar to gymnastics",response_option:"acrobatics",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a children’s summer camp. Today a new group of children arrived. They need to sign up for different activities. The camp offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA kid walks up to a teacher and asks:",question:"Is there a gymnastics class?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no gymnastics class.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a gymnastics class",competitor:"an acrobatics class",sameCategory:"a karate class",otherCategory:"a watercolor painting class",character_template:"The teacher replies:"},{submission_id:4695,age:41,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:250508,experiment_end_time:1672237158920,experiment_start_time:1672236908412,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:36855,settingName:"interior",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"interior-green",answer:"Unfortunately I don't have Aloe Vera, but I do have an agave plant you might like.",response_option:"agave",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"Your aunt likes to decorate the house and often crafts decorations herself. She often gives away crafts and plants to friends and family. Your aunt currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits your aunt and asks her:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera plant",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory:"tulips",otherCategory:"an oil painting",character_template:"Your aunt replies:"},{submission_id:4730,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:280125,experiment_end_time:1672240409731,experiment_start_time:1672240129606,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:31791,settingName:"bar",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-tea",answer:"Unfortunately no we don't, but we do have iced coffee",response_option:"iced coffee",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have iced tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have iced tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"iced tea",competitor:"iced coffee",sameCategory:"soda",otherCategory:"Chardonnay",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4672,age:33,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"NA",experiment_duration:215988,experiment_end_time:1672171791741,experiment_start_time:1672171575753,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:38640,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-muscle",answer:"Unfortunately not - the most similar item we have is a kayak.",response_option:"kayak",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent canoes?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent canoes.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"canoes",competitor:"kayaks",sameCategory:"pedal boats",otherCategory:"water ski equipment",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4751,age:28,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:147153,experiment_end_time:1672243869023,experiment_start_time:1672243721870,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:16779,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"Unfortunately not but we do sell cigarettes.",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4700,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:361322,experiment_end_time:1672237280621,experiment_start_time:1672236919299,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:47885,settingName:"bar",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"Unfortunately not, but we do have Chardonnay?",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4709,age:24,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:156644,experiment_end_time:1672240277181,experiment_start_time:1672240120537,gender:"male",languages:"NA",responseTime:35238,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-sweets",answer:"Unfortunately not, but we do have gingerbread available.",response_option:"gingerbread",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cookies?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cookies.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cookies",competitor:"gingerbread",sameCategory:"granola bars",otherCategory:"cigarettes",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4758,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:232156,experiment_end_time:1672243966180,experiment_start_time:1672243734024,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:48488,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"Unfortunately not, but, may I interest you in some of our top of the range kickboxing classes? You may find that it gives you the adrenaline rush - and fitness regime - that you're looking for.",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4713,age:26,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:190952,experiment_end_time:1672240314740,experiment_start_time:1672240123788,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:64765,settingName:"bookingAgency",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bookingAgency-highClassAccommodation",answer:"Unfortunately there are no five-star hotels available for a single room, but we have a great option for a suite in a four-star hotel.",response_option:"four-star hotel",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a travel booking agency in a medium-sized tourist town. The following types of accommodation are still available for tomorrow night:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAn older man walks in and asks the agent:",question:"Is a single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a single room in a five-star hotel",competitor:"a suite in a four-star hotel",sameCategory:"an expensive apartment close to the city",otherCategory:"a room in a cheap bed-and-breakfast",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4676,age:39,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:293514,experiment_end_time:1672171892794,experiment_start_time:1672171599280,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:40426,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-xl",answer:"Unfortunately there is no Tiger, but the lions are good!",response_option:"lion",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the tiger?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, they don’t have a tiger here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a tiger",competitor:"a lion",sameCategory:"a giraffe",otherCategory:"iguanas",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4745,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:1448945,experiment_end_time:1672241577263,experiment_start_time:1672240128318,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:63218,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"Unfortunately we don't have raspberry cake but we have raspberry pie if you are interested to try.",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4744,age:50,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:679177,experiment_end_time:1672240884035,experiment_start_time:1672240204858,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:236131,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"Unfortunately we don't. However, we do offer kickboxing classes which focused on kicking and punching if you'd like to consider.",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4717,age:55,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:197577,experiment_end_time:1672240332052,experiment_start_time:1672240134475,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:34488,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"Unfortunately, we do not sell cigars, but we do have cigarettes for sale.",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4764,age:35,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:511266,experiment_end_time:1672244258996,experiment_start_time:1672243747730,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:89432,settingName:"bookingAgency",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bookingAgency-highClassAccommodation",answer:"Unfortunatly we don't but I can offer you a suite in a 4 star hotel.",response_option:"four-star hotel",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a travel booking agency in a medium-sized tourist town. The following types of accommodation are still available for tomorrow night:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAn older man walks in and asks the agent:",question:"Is a single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a single room in a five-star hotel",competitor:"a suite in a four-star hotel",sameCategory:"an expensive apartment close to the city",otherCategory:"a room in a cheap bed-and-breakfast",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4673,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:210370,experiment_end_time:1672171793507,experiment_start_time:1672171583137,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:25155,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"We actually have a raspberry pie today instead. Would you like to try it?",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4657,age:62,comments:"Nothing to add.",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:307308,experiment_end_time:1672168785168,experiment_start_time:1672168477860,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:78970,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",answer:"We are hosting a club event with a hip hop DJ, would that be the one you were thinking of?",response_option:"hip hop DJ",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory:"live jazz music",otherCategory:"a circus show",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4614,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:142055,experiment_end_time:1672164834373,experiment_start_time:1672164692318,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:32390,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-xl",answer:"We can go and see the lions which are similar to tigers.",response_option:"lion",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the tiger?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, they don’t have a tiger here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a tiger",competitor:"a lion",sameCategory:"a giraffe",otherCategory:"iguanas",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4742,age:42,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:221861,experiment_end_time:1672240750257,experiment_start_time:1672240528396,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:32466,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"We currently do not have raspberry cake but we do have raspberry pie.",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4636,age:34,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:327744,experiment_end_time:1672165996743,experiment_start_time:1672165668999,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:70191,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-yoga",answer:"We currently don't offer yoga classes, pilates classes are very similar if you wish to try it out.",response_option:"pilates",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer yoga classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have yoga.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"yoga classes",competitor:"a pilates class",sameCategory:"zumba classes",otherCategory:"kickboxing",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4653,age:45,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:217021,experiment_end_time:1672168702974,experiment_start_time:1672168485953,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:27015,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"We do a kickboxing class.",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4673,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:210370,experiment_end_time:1672171793507,experiment_start_time:1672171583137,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:33464,settingName:"books",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"We do have a book of French love letters.  Would that interest you?",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4694,age:25,comments:"i enjoyed this id like to do more like this",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:213829,experiment_end_time:1672237113708,experiment_start_time:1672236899879,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:54641,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-motor",answer:"We do have a range of water ski equipment, but I will have to double check if we specifically have jet skis avaliable at the moment",response_option:"water ski equipment",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent jet skis?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent jet skis.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"jet skis",competitor:"water ski equipment",sameCategory:"rubber dinghies",otherCategory:"kayaks",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4696,age:33,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:264941,experiment_end_time:1672237175619,experiment_start_time:1672236910678,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:46607,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pizza",answer:"We do have cheese pizza available.",response_option:"cheese",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have veggie pizza?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have veggie pizza today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"veggie pizza",competitor:"cheese pizza",sameCategory:"pepperoni pizza",otherCategory:"raspberry pie",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4701,age:20,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:401872,experiment_end_time:1672237308802,experiment_start_time:1672236906930,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:71084,settingName:"bookingAgency",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bookingAgency-highClassAccommodation",answer:"We do not have a five star hotel available for tomorrow night but there is a four star suite in a hotel nearby",response_option:"four-star hotel",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a travel booking agency in a medium-sized tourist town. The following types of accommodation are still available for tomorrow night:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAn older man walks in and asks the agent:",question:"Is a single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a single room in a five-star hotel",competitor:"a suite in a four-star hotel",sameCategory:"an expensive apartment close to the city",otherCategory:"a room in a cheap bed-and-breakfast",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4713,age:26,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:190952,experiment_end_time:1672240314740,experiment_start_time:1672240123788,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:36975,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-console",answer:"We do not have a PlayStation in stock, however we do have an Xbox that works almost the same as a PlayStation.",response_option:"Xbox",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a PlayStation?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a PlayStation.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a PlayStation",competitor:"an Xbox",sameCategory:"a Gameboy",otherCategory:"a MacBook Air",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4696,age:33,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:264941,experiment_end_time:1672237175619,experiment_start_time:1672236910678,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:69761,settingName:"clothing",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"clothing-acc",answer:"We do not have any earrings in stock at the moment. If you're interested in jewellery though, we do have some necklacke's.",response_option:"necklace",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a small designer clothing store. The store currently has the following items in stock:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer comes in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have any earrings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any earrings.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"earrings",competitor:"necklaces",sameCategory:"sunglasses",otherCategory:"shorts",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4714,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:180206,experiment_end_time:1672240318791,experiment_start_time:1672240138585,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:19708,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"We do not have hamsters but we have gerbils",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4624,age:22,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:111973,experiment_end_time:1672165025747,experiment_start_time:1672164913774,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:19241,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-sweets",answer:"We do not sell cookies. However, we do sell gingerbread which may suit you.",response_option:"gingerbread",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cookies?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cookies.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cookies",competitor:"gingerbread",sameCategory:"granola bars",otherCategory:"cigarettes",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4681,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:245085,experiment_end_time:1672172087584,experiment_start_time:1672171842499,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:31248,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"We do offer kickboxing classes here.",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4722,age:76,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:221967,experiment_end_time:1672240350422,experiment_start_time:1672240128455,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:37625,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"We don't but have you considered a MacBook Air instead?",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4734,age:40,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:394492,experiment_end_time:1672240506248,experiment_start_time:1672240111756,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:25625,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"We don't but we do have a delicious raspberry pie",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4674,age:25,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:218125,experiment_end_time:1672171823718,experiment_start_time:1672171605593,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:18626,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"We don't but would you be interested in any cigarettes?",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4729,age:24,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:264807,experiment_end_time:1672240412648,experiment_start_time:1672240147841,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:50194,settingName:"kidsActivities",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"kidsActivities-sports",answer:"We don't have a gymnastics class, but we do have an acrobatics class. Would you like to sign up for that?",response_option:"acrobatics",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a children’s summer camp. Today a new group of children arrived. They need to sign up for different activities. The camp offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA kid walks up to a teacher and asks:",question:"Is there a gymnastics class?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no gymnastics class.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a gymnastics class",competitor:"an acrobatics class",sameCategory:"a karate class",otherCategory:"a watercolor painting class",character_template:"The teacher replies:"},{submission_id:4757,age:57,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:233601,experiment_end_time:1672243964113,experiment_start_time:1672243730512,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:70645,settingName:"books",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"We don’t have a love poem but we do have a book of French love letters if that’s any use to you?",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4638,age:39,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:363856,experiment_end_time:1672166025082,experiment_start_time:1672165661226,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:54111,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pizza",answer:"We don't have a vegetable pizza today. If you are vegetarian we have a cheese pizza. Is that good for you?",response_option:"cheese",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have veggie pizza?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have veggie pizza today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"veggie pizza",competitor:"cheese pizza",sameCategory:"pepperoni pizza",otherCategory:"raspberry pie",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4679,age:36,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:371599,experiment_end_time:1672171954719,experiment_start_time:1672171583120,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:48993,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"We don't have any cake today but we have a beautiful raspberry pie that I'd reccomend.",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4636,age:34,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:327744,experiment_end_time:1672165996743,experiment_start_time:1672165668999,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:76216,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-dogs",answer:"We don't have any Dalmatians, if you are looking for a dog of similar size we do have golden retrievers.",response_option:"golden retriever",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any Dalmatians?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any dalmatians.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"dalmatians",competitor:"golden retrievers",sameCategory:"chihuahuas",otherCategory:"gerbils",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4709,age:24,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:156644,experiment_end_time:1672240277181,experiment_start_time:1672240120537,gender:"male",languages:"NA",responseTime:27612,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"We don't have any hamsters, sadly. However, we do have gerbils if that is okay?",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4723,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:235583,experiment_end_time:1672240357967,experiment_start_time:1672240122384,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:38085,settingName:"books",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-fantasy",answer:"We don't have any in stock right now I'm afraid, but we do have this mystery novel that you might be interested in",response_option:"mystery",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you sell psychological thrillers?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t sell psychological thrillers.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"psychological thrillers",competitor:"mystery novels",sameCategory:"adventure novels",otherCategory:"books of French love letters",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4629,age:45,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:166231,experiment_end_time:1672165840245,experiment_start_time:1672165674014,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:26999,settingName:"kidsActivities",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"kidsActivities-sports",answer:"We don't have gymnastics but we do have acrobatics",response_option:"acrobatics",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a children’s summer camp. Today a new group of children arrived. They need to sign up for different activities. The camp offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA kid walks up to a teacher and asks:",question:"Is there a gymnastics class?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no gymnastics class.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a gymnastics class",competitor:"an acrobatics class",sameCategory:"a karate class",otherCategory:"a watercolor painting class",character_template:"The teacher replies:"},{submission_id:4709,age:24,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:156644,experiment_end_time:1672240277181,experiment_start_time:1672240120537,gender:"male",languages:"NA",responseTime:22418,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"We don't offer boxing classes but we do offer kickboxing classes.",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4623,age:55,comments:"Just to say good luck",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:312976,experiment_end_time:1672165009891,experiment_start_time:1672164696915,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:51478,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-muscle",answer:"We don't rent canoes but kayaks are similar",response_option:"kayak",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent canoes?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent canoes.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"canoes",competitor:"kayaks",sameCategory:"pedal boats",otherCategory:"water ski equipment",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4723,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:235583,experiment_end_time:1672240357967,experiment_start_time:1672240122384,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:46891,settingName:"clothing",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"clothing-acc",answer:"We don't right now, but if it's jewellery you're after then our necklace section is just over here",response_option:"necklace",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a small designer clothing store. The store currently has the following items in stock:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer comes in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have any earrings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any earrings.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"earrings",competitor:"necklaces",sameCategory:"sunglasses",otherCategory:"shorts",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4692,age:20,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:194401,experiment_end_time:1672237099998,experiment_start_time:1672236905597,gender:"other",languages:"English",responseTime:30662,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"We don't sorry, but we do have gerbils that you might be interested in?",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4692,age:20,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:194401,experiment_end_time:1672237099998,experiment_start_time:1672236905597,gender:"other",languages:"English",responseTime:30053,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"We don't sorry, but we do have kickboxing instead if that's something you're interested in.",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4723,age:32,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:235583,experiment_end_time:1672240357967,experiment_start_time:1672240122384,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:55890,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-console",answer:"We don't, would you be interested in an Xbox?",response_option:"Xbox",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a PlayStation?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a PlayStation.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a PlayStation",competitor:"an Xbox",sameCategory:"a Gameboy",otherCategory:"a MacBook Air",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4738,age:31,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:112630,experiment_end_time:1672240553614,experiment_start_time:1672240440984,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:13768,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"We dont, we do have cigarettes for sale.",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4757,age:57,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:233601,experiment_end_time:1672243964113,experiment_start_time:1672243730512,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:29034,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",answer:"We have a circus show that would be suitable for children.",response_option:"circus",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory:"a trade fare",otherCategory:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4691,age:47,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:186240,experiment_end_time:1672237092189,experiment_start_time:1672236905949,gender:"male",languages:"NA",responseTime:39659,settingName:"electronics",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"electronics-laptop",answer:"We have a Macbook Air, will that interest you?",response_option:"MacBook Air",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a second hand electronics store. The store currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory:"a desktop computer",otherCategory:"an Xbox",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4643,age:60,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:678649,experiment_end_time:1672166354788,experiment_start_time:1672165676139,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:110730,settingName:"kidsActivities",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"kidsActivities-sports",answer:"We have an acrobatics class which is similar to gymnastics.",response_option:"acrobatics",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a children’s summer camp. Today a new group of children arrived. They need to sign up for different activities. The camp offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA kid walks up to a teacher and asks:",question:"Is there a gymnastics class?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no gymnastics class.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a gymnastics class",competitor:"an acrobatics class",sameCategory:"a karate class",otherCategory:"a watercolor painting class",character_template:"The teacher replies:"},{submission_id:4635,age:39,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:294443,experiment_end_time:1672165986021,experiment_start_time:1672165691578,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:65512,settingName:"books",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"We have books of French love letters that may contain poems.",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4695,age:41,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:250508,experiment_end_time:1672237158920,experiment_start_time:1672236908412,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:31492,settingName:"books",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"We have books of French love letters, some of these may contain poems. you may find them interesting.",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4674,age:25,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:218125,experiment_end_time:1672171823718,experiment_start_time:1672171605593,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:30133,settingName:"books",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"We have books with french love letters, would you be interested in those?",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4605,age:23,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:247064,experiment_end_time:1672163430843,experiment_start_time:1672163183779,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:45019,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pizza",answer:"We have cheese pizza which is vegeterian, however we do not have any pizzas with vegetable toppings.",response_option:"cheese",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have veggie pizza?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have veggie pizza today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"veggie pizza",competitor:"cheese pizza",sameCategory:"pepperoni pizza",otherCategory:"raspberry pie",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4663,age:22,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:344648,experiment_end_time:1672169075225,experiment_start_time:1672168730577,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:48418,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"we have cigarettes",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4659,age:35,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:344579,experiment_end_time:1672168821108,experiment_start_time:1672168476529,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:16331,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"We have ciggerattes",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4685,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:95714,experiment_end_time:1672237002197,experiment_start_time:1672236906483,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:14562,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",answer:"We have gerbils, if you prefer?",response_option:"gerbil",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory:"ferrets",otherCategory:"golden retrievers",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4648,age:31,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:175066,experiment_end_time:1672168658394,experiment_start_time:1672168483328,gender:"male",languages:"English, Polish",responseTime:37293,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-muscle",answer:"We have kayaks only, if that's ok?",response_option:"kayak",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent canoes?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent canoes.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"canoes",competitor:"kayaks",sameCategory:"pedal boats",otherCategory:"water ski equipment",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4653,age:45,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:217021,experiment_end_time:1672168702974,experiment_start_time:1672168485953,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:18761,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-muscle",answer:"We have kayaks.",response_option:"kayak",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent canoes?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent canoes.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"canoes",competitor:"kayaks",sameCategory:"pedal boats",otherCategory:"water ski equipment",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4617,age:24,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:183518,experiment_end_time:1672164871173,experiment_start_time:1672164687655,gender:"female",languages:"English, Japanese",responseTime:25192,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"We have kickboxing classes - would you be interested in that?",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4691,age:47,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:186240,experiment_end_time:1672237092189,experiment_start_time:1672236905949,gender:"male",languages:"NA",responseTime:31038,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"We have raspberry pie",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4659,age:35,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:344579,experiment_end_time:1672168821108,experiment_start_time:1672168476529,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:22059,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pie",answer:"We have raspberry pie which is lovely",response_option:"raspberry pie",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory:"cheese pizza",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4640,age:62,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:444611,experiment_end_time:1672166112109,experiment_start_time:1672165667498,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:77716,settingName:"clothing",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"clothing-acc",answer:"we have sold out until next weeks new stock arrives, how about a necklace but be quick as they are selling out too.",response_option:"necklace",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a small designer clothing store. The store currently has the following items in stock:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer comes in and asks the sales assistant:",question:"Do you have any earrings?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any earrings.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"earrings",competitor:"necklaces",sameCategory:"sunglasses",otherCategory:"shorts",character_template:"The sales assistant replies:"},{submission_id:4672,age:33,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"NA",experiment_duration:215988,experiment_end_time:1672171791741,experiment_start_time:1672171575753,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:50330,settingName:"books",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-fantasy",answer:"We have some mystery books that could also be considered thrillers.",response_option:"mystery",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you sell psychological thrillers?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t sell psychological thrillers.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"psychological thrillers",competitor:"mystery novels",sameCategory:"adventure novels",otherCategory:"books of French love letters",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4716,age:24,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:204818,experiment_end_time:1672240331817,experiment_start_time:1672240126999,gender:"female",languages:"english",responseTime:24544,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"we offer kick-boxing classes but not boxing classes unfortunately",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4618,age:29,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:195248,experiment_end_time:1672164888791,experiment_start_time:1672164693543,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:23698,settingName:"bar",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"We only have Chardonnay I’m afraid",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4737,age:69,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:415692,experiment_end_time:1672240553259,experiment_start_time:1672240137567,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:79884,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:5,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-muscle",answer:"We rent kayaks which I am sure you will be happy with.",response_option:"kayak",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent canoes?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent canoes.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"canoes",competitor:"kayaks",sameCategory:"pedal boats",otherCategory:"water ski equipment",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4738,age:31,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:112630,experiment_end_time:1672240553614,experiment_start_time:1672240440984,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:24383,settingName:"waterSport",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"waterSport-motor",answer:"We rent water ski equipment",response_option:"water ski equipment",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks the agent:",question:"Do you rent jet skis?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent jet skis.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"jet skis",competitor:"water ski equipment",sameCategory:"rubber dinghies",otherCategory:"kayaks",character_template:"The agent replies:"},{submission_id:4738,age:31,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:112630,experiment_end_time:1672240553614,experiment_start_time:1672240440984,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:16921,settingName:"bar",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"bar-whiteWine",answer:"We serve Chardonnay if that is any good to you.",response_option:"Chardonnay",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says to the bartender:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Sauvignon Blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory:"craft beer",otherCategory:"iced coffee",character_template:"The bartender replies:"},{submission_id:4674,age:25,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated High-school",experiment_duration:218125,experiment_end_time:1672171823718,experiment_start_time:1672171605593,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:42769,settingName:"petAdoption",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"petAdoption-dogs",answer:"We unfortnatly don't but do have golden retrievers that are similar in energy level and size.",response_option:"golden retriever",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at an adoption center for rescued animals. Currently there are the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks an employee:",question:"Do you have any Dalmatians?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any dalmatians.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"dalmatians",competitor:"golden retrievers",sameCategory:"chihuahuas",otherCategory:"gerbils",character_template:"The employee replies:"},{submission_id:4676,age:39,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:293514,experiment_end_time:1672171892794,experiment_start_time:1672171599280,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:28662,settingName:"books",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"We've got french love letters will that do?",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4698,age:58,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:295519,experiment_end_time:1672237210045,experiment_start_time:1672236914526,gender:"male",languages:"english",responseTime:55752,settingName:"touristInfo",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",answer:"Well do you class a club event with a hip hop DJ as electronic?",response_option:"hip hop DJ",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks the consultant:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory:"live jazz music",otherCategory:"a circus show",character_template:"The consultant replies:"},{submission_id:4764,age:35,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:511266,experiment_end_time:1672244258996,experiment_start_time:1672243747730,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:78827,settingName:"zoo",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"zoo-reptiles",answer:"Well we can go the the iguanas and ask the people who look after them if we can see the chameleon.",response_option:"iguana",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You and a group of friends are at the zoo today. You all carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne friend with an eight-year-old kid arrives late. The kid runs up to one of your friend impatiently and asks:",question:"Can we see the chameleon?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, they don't have chameleons here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a chameleon",competitor:"iguanas",sameCategory:"turtles",otherCategory:"a lion",character_template:"Your friend replies:"},{submission_id:4766,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:663522,experiment_end_time:1672244426512,experiment_start_time:1672243762990,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:145001,settingName:"books",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-romance",answer:"Yes i do. I have books of French love letters written in poems",response_option:"French love letters",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory:"historical dramas",otherCategory:"mystery novels",character_template:"The cashier replies:"},{submission_id:4629,age:45,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:166231,experiment_end_time:1672165840245,experiment_start_time:1672165674014,gender:"female",languages:"English",responseTime:11359,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:3,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pizza",answer:"Yes we have a cheese piazza",response_option:"cheese",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have veggie pizza?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have veggie pizza today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"veggie pizza",competitor:"cheese pizza",sameCategory:"pepperoni pizza",otherCategory:"raspberry pie",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4766,age:30,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:663522,experiment_end_time:1672244426512,experiment_start_time:1672243762990,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:80924,settingName:"dutyFree",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",answer:"Yes, i sell Cigarettes",response_option:"cigarettes",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are on an old-fashioned international flight. The flight attendants are selling duty-free items to passengers. The flight attendants currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs a flight attendant walks by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory:"gin",otherCategory:"gingerbread",character_template:"The flight attendant replies:"},{submission_id:4721,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Higher degree",experiment_duration:222618,experiment_end_time:1672240345239,experiment_start_time:1672240122621,gender:"female",languages:"English, French",responseTime:42314,settingName:"gymActivities",trialNr:1,trial_type:"main",itemName:"gym-boxing",answer:"Yes, we do offer kickboxing classes. Would you be interested in learning more about these?",response_option:"kickboxing",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks the receptionist:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory:"karate classes",otherCategory:"pilates",character_template:"The receptionist replies:"},{submission_id:4707,age:38,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:119012,experiment_end_time:1672240246245,experiment_start_time:1672240127233,gender:"male",languages:"NA",responseTime:18416,settingName:"cafe",trialNr:4,trial_type:"main",itemName:"cafe-pizza",answer:"Yes, we have cheese pizza.",response_option:"cheese",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks the waiter:",question:"Do you have veggie pizza?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have veggie pizza today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"veggie pizza",competitor:"cheese pizza",sameCategory:"pepperoni pizza",otherCategory:"raspberry pie",character_template:"The waiter replies:"},{submission_id:4758,age:27,comments:"NA",correct_response:"main",education:"Graduated College",experiment_duration:232156,experiment_end_time:1672243966180,experiment_start_time:1672243734024,gender:"male",languages:"English",responseTime:40320,settingName:"books",trialNr:2,trial_type:"main",itemName:"books-fantasy",answer:"You may find our mystery novels to be your liking, but, if not, I do have a few recommendations you may find elsewhere.",response_option:"mystery",option_category:"competitor",category:"competitor",vignette_start:"You are at a bookshop in a small town. The shop currently has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks the cashier:",question:"Do you sell psychological thrillers?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t sell psychological thrillers.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"psychological thrillers",competitor:"mystery novels",sameCategory:"adventure novels",otherCategory:"books of French love letters",character_template:"The cashier replies:"}]},5514:function(e){e.exports=[{itemName:"jobCenter-office",settingName:"jobCenter",vignette_start:"You are working at the job center consultation desk and help people find open vacancies. Please type ‘teacher’ in each text area. Currently the following positions are available at local businesses:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA man walks in and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"had",question:"Is there an open accountant job?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no accountant job open.",answer_template:"There is *.",answer:"filler",itemQuestion:"an accountant job",competitor:"a bookkeeper job",sameCategory:"a manager assistant job",otherCategory:"a car mechanic job",correct_response:"teacher"},{itemName:"jobCenter-engineer",settingName:"jobCenter",vignette_start:"You are working at the job center consultation desk and help people find open vacancies. Please type ‘teacher’ in each text area. Currently the following positions are available at local businesses:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA man walks in and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"had",question:"Is there an electrical mechanic job open?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no electrical mechanic job open.",answer_template:"There is *.",answer:"filler",itemQuestion:"an electrical mechanic job",competitor:"an electrician job",sameCategory:"a car mechanic job",otherCategory:"a secretary job",correct_response:"teacher"},{itemName:"art-painting",settingName:"art",vignette_start:"You work at an art shop. You are hosting an exhibition sale by a local artist. The artist has",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘sculpture’ in each text area. \\n\\nA customer takes a look around and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the right. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"got",question:"Are there any acrylic paintings for sale?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, there are no acrylic paintings.",answer_template:"There are *.",answer:"filler",itemQuestion:"acrylic paintings",competitor:"gouache paintings",sameCategory:"oil paintings",otherCategory:"pencil drawings",correct_response:"sculpture"},{itemName:"art-drawing",settingName:"art",vignette_start:"You work at an art shop. You are hosting an exhibition sale by a local artist. The artist has",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘sculpture’ in each text area. \\n\\nA customer takes a look around and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the right. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"got",question:"Are there any ink drawings for sale?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, there are no ink drawings.",answer_template:"There are *.",answer:"filler",itemQuestion:"ink drawings",competitor:"pencil drawings",sameCategory:"crayon drawings",otherCategory:"oil paintings",correct_response:"sculpture"},{itemName:"carRental-fun",settingName:"carRental",vignette_start:"You are working in a private car rental agency. Please type ‘motorcycle’ in each text area. For today, the following types of vehicles are still available on site:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"got",question:"Do you have a Porsche for rent today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have a Porsche on site today.",answer_template:"We have *.",answer:"filler",itemQuestion:"a Porsche",competitor:"a Ferrari",sameCategory:"a BMW convertible",otherCategory:"a medium-sized delivery truck",correct_response:"motorcycle"},{itemName:"carRental-moving",settingName:"carRental",vignette_start:"You are working in a private car rental agency. Please type ‘motorcycle’ in each text area. For today, the following types of vehicles are still available on site:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"got",question:"Is a moving truck available on site?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have a moving truck on site today.",answer_template:"We have *.",answer:"filler",itemQuestion:"a moving truck",competitor:"a medium-sized delivery truck",sameCategory:"a Volkswagen camper",otherCategory:"a Ferrari",correct_response:"motorcycle"},{itemName:"music-hardrock",settingName:"music",vignette_start:"You are driving in a car with your neighbor. Please type ‘classic’ in each text area. The car only has an old CD player. You have the following styles of music:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour neighbor asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the right. Suppose someone wants to listen to",priorElicitation_question:"listened to",question:"Do you have any hard rock?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have any hard rock.",answer_template:"I have some *.",answer:"filler",itemQuestion:"hard rock",competitor:"classic rock",sameCategory:"heavy metal",otherCategory:"cool jazz",correct_response:"classic"},{itemName:"music-softrock",settingName:"music",vignette_start:"You are driving in a car with your neighbor. Please type ‘classic’ in each text area. The car only has an old CD player. You have the following styles of music:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour neighbor asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the right. Suppose someone wants to listen to",priorElicitation_question:"listened to",question:"Do you have any soft rock?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have any soft rock.",answer_template:"I have some *.",answer:"filler",itemQuestion:"soft rock",competitor:"cool jazz",sameCategory:"soul jazz",otherCategory:"death metal",correct_response:"classic"},{itemName:"airport-usa",settingName:"airport",vignette_start:"You are a customer service agent helping to book flights. Today there is ",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘London’ in each text area.\\n\\nA customer asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to book",priorElicitation_question:"booked",question:"Do you have an afternoon flight to Boston?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have an afternoon flight to Boston today.",answer_template:"We have *.",answer:"filler",itemQuestion:"an afternoon flight to Boston",competitor:"a morning flight to Boston",sameCategory:"an afternoon flight to San Francisco",otherCategory:"a flight to Australia",correct_response:"London"},{itemName:"airport-europe-UPDATED",settingName:"airport",vignette_start:"You are a customer service agent helping to book flights. Today there is",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘London’ in each text area.\\n\\nA customer asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to book",priorElicitation_question:"booked",question:"Do you have a morning flight to Madrid?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have a morning flight to Madrid today.",answer_template:"We have *.",answer:"filler",itemQuestion:"a morning flight to Madrid",competitor:"a morning flight to Barcelona with connections to other airports",sameCategory:"an evening flight to Paris",otherCategory:"a flight to New York",correct_response:"London"}]},9319:function(e){e.exports=[{"":0,itemName:"chair-repair",settingName:"chair",question:"Do you have a chair?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a chair. I have  a ladder.",vignette_start:"You have a new neighbor who will be moving into the apartment on the ground floor of your house. You see your new neighbor cleaning his windows before moving in. When walking out of the building you see him trying to reach the top of the window that he is cleaning. In the shared utility closet of the apartment building there are  ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nWhen your neighbor sees your other neighbor in front of the house, they greet them and ask:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your other neighbor replies:",itemQuestion:"a chair",competitor:"a ladder",sameCategory:"a stool",otherCategory:"a broom",mostSimilar:"a leather recliner"},{"":1,itemName:"chair-party",settingName:"chair",question:"Do you have a chair?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a chair. I have a stool.",vignette_start:"Your neighbor is hosting a dinner party with a lot of guests at their apartment on the ground floor. The house does not have an elevator. All neighbors are also invited. As more guests arrive, your neighbor runs out of seating options. In the shared utility closet of the apartment building there are ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nWhen your neighbor sees your other neighbor in front of the house, they greet them and ask:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your other neighbor replies:",itemQuestion:"a chair",competitor:"a stool",sameCategory:"a ladder",otherCategory:"a broom",mostSimilar:"a leather recliner"},{"":2,itemName:"blanket-sleepover",settingName:"blanket",question:"Do you have a blanket?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a blanket. I have a sleeping bag.",vignette_start:"Your roommate is having a sleepover with some friends on the weekend. They are preparing everything for hosting the guests since they don’t host many guests very often. The following items are in the attic of the house: ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour roommate asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your other roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"a blanket",competitor:"a sleeping bag",sameCategory:"some bubble wrap",otherCategory:"a carpet",mostSimilar:"a pillow"},{"":3,itemName:"blanket-transportation",settingName:"blanket",question:"Do you have a blanket?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a blanket. I have some bubble wrap.",vignette_start:"Your roommate is moving to another apartment and is packing her things. She has a large mirror that she needs to pack for transportation. The following items are in the attic of the house: ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour roommate asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your other roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"a blanket",competitor:"some bubble wrap",sameCategory:"a sleeping bag",otherCategory:"a carpet",mostSimilar:"a pillow"},{"":4,itemName:"box-muffins",settingName:"box",question:"Do you have a box?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a box. I have a cake container.",vignette_start:"You and some friends got together to bake muffins and cookies. Your friends want to take home some of the pastries, but forgot to bring containers. In the pantry, there are ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs your friends want to head out they ask:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"a box",competitor:"a cake container",sameCategory:"a ziplock bag",otherCategory:"a tote bag",mostSimilar:"a carton"},{"":5,itemName:"box-bbq",settingName:"box",question:"Do you have a box?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a box. I have a ziplock bag.",vignette_start:"You and some friends had a BBQ and there are quite a lot of leftovers. Your friends want to take home some of the food, but forgot to bring containers. In the pantry, there are ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs your friends want to head out they ask:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"a box",competitor:"a ziplock bag",sameCategory:"a cake container",otherCategory:"a tote bag",mostSimilar:"a carton"},{"":6,itemName:"sugar-coffee",settingName:"sugar",question:"Do you have sugar?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have sugar. I have sweetener tablets.",vignette_start:"Your roommate is having lunch with some friends at your house. They just finished eating and your roommate is making coffee now. In the pantry there are ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne of the friends asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"sugar",competitor:"sweetener tablets",sameCategory:"agave syrup",otherCategory:"salt",mostSimilar:"honey"},{"":7,itemName:"sugar-baking",settingName:"sugar",question:"Do you have sugar?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have sugar. I have agave syrup.",vignette_start:"It’s Christmas time. Your roommate just finished baking a big batch of cookies, so they ran out of most of the ingredients. Your neighbor is also baking and seems to have run out of some ingredients during the process. Your roommate has left ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour neighbor rings at your door and asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"sugar",competitor:"agave syrup",sameCategory:"sweetener tablets",otherCategory:"salt",mostSimilar:"honey"},{"":8,itemName:"handkerchief-injury",settingName:"handkerchief",question:"Do you have a handkerchief?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a handkerchief. I have some band aids.",vignette_start:"You and your friend are taking a walk in the park. As you walk by a playground, you see an elderly person comforting a child who just fell down and hurt their knee. In their backpack, your friend has  ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nThe elderly person walks towards you and asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your friend replies:",itemQuestion:"a handkerchief",competitor:"some band aids",sameCategory:"some wet wipes",otherCategory:"a cell phone",mostSimilar:"paper napkins"},{"":9,itemName:"handkerchief-sauce",settingName:"handkerchief",question:"Do you have a handkerchief?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a handkerchief. I have some wet wipes.",vignette_start:"You and your friend are traveling by train. Your elderly seat neighbor just started eating a sandwich and spilled some sauce on their sweater. In their backpack, your friend has  ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour seat neighbor turns to you and asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your friend replies:",itemQuestion:"a handkerchief",competitor:"some wet wipes",sameCategory:"some band aids",otherCategory:"a cell phone",mostSimilar:"paper napkins"},{"":10,itemName:"broom-renovation",settingName:"broom",question:"Do you have a broom?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a broom. I have a vacuum cleaner.",vignette_start:"Your neighbors recently finished renovating their apartment. They are now cleaning up after renovation. You heard that they don’t have any household supplies yet since they plan to move in next week. In your apartment, you have ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOne of your neighbors rings your bell and asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate answers the door and replies:",itemQuestion:"a broom",competitor:"a vacuum cleaner",sameCategory:"a shovel",otherCategory:"a lamp",mostSimilar:"a hand brush"},{"":11,itemName:"broom-snow",settingName:"broom",question:"Do you have a broom?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a broom. I have a shovel.",vignette_start:"You live in a suburban house and share the driveway to your house with your neighbors. You take turns taking care of the road. You just woke up, looked out of the window and noticed that it snowed over the night, which is not very common in your area. This week it’s your neighbors’ turn to take care of the driveway. In your house, you happen to have ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour neighbor rings at your door and asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate answers the door and replies:",itemQuestion:"a broom",competitor:"a shovel",sameCategory:"a vacuum cleaner",otherCategory:"a lamp",mostSimilar:"a hand brush"},{"":12,itemName:"sweatpants-sleepover",settingName:"sweatpants",question:"Do you have sweatpants?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have sweatpants. I have pyjamas.",vignette_start:"You and your roommate have some friends over at your place. They evening got long and it is already way past midnight. Therefore, one person who lives far away decided to stay over. In you closet you have ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nOnce other guests left, he wants to change for the night and asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"sweatpants",competitor:"pyjamas",sameCategory:"shorts",otherCategory:"towels",mostSimilar:"a pair of leggings"},{"":13,itemName:"sweatpants-spill",settingName:"sweatpants",question:"Do you have sweatpants?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have sweatpants. I have shorts.",vignette_start:"It is a hot summer weekend. You and your roommate have some friends over at your garden for a dinner party. One guest just spilled coffee on his pants. In your closet, you have ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nThe guest asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"sweatpants",competitor:"shorts",sameCategory:"pyjamas",otherCategory:"towels",mostSimilar:"a pair of leggings"},{"":14,itemName:"umbrella-summer",settingName:"umbrella",question:"Do you have an umbrella?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have an umbrella. I have sunscreen.",vignette_start:"Your house has a beautiful garden and a pool. During the summer you often have friends over in the garden. Today is a really hot day, and a friend wants to lie outside in the garden but doesn’t want to get sunburned. In your storage closet in the house, you have ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nThe friend asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"an umbrella",competitor:"sunscreen",sameCategory:"a rain jacket",otherCategory:"a tent",mostSimilar:"a plastic bike cover"},{"":15,itemName:"umbrella-rain",settingName:"umbrella",question:"Do you have an umbrella?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have an umbrella. I have a rain jacket.",vignette_start:"You and your roommate just had coffee with some friends at your house. Now they want to take off but a heavy rain just started. In your storage closet in the house, you have ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour friend asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"an umbrella",competitor:"a rain jacket",sameCategory:"sunscreen",otherCategory:"a tent",mostSimilar:"a plastic bike cover"},{"":16,itemName:"postit-board",settingName:"postit",question:"Are there post-its?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, we don't have post-its. There is a whiteboard marker.",vignette_start:"Your colleague is organizing a workshop at the office. They want to collect ideas for a new product with the team and gather everyone's thoughts on at the office whiteboard. At the office, there are ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour colleague asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Another colleague replies:",itemQuestion:"post-its",competitor:"a whiteboard marker",sameCategory:"sticky bookmarks",otherCategory:"an eraser",mostSimilar:"a notebook"},{"":17,itemName:"postit-reading",settingName:"postit",question:"Are there post-its?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, we don't have post-its. There are sticky bookmarks.",vignette_start:"Your colleague at the office has to read through a lot of documents and wants to take some notes. At the office, there are ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour colleague asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Another colleague replies:",itemQuestion:"post-its",competitor:"sticky bookmarks",sameCategory:"a whiteboard marker",otherCategory:"an eraser",mostSimilar:"a notebook"},{"":18,itemName:"pot-garden",settingName:"pot",question:"Do you have a pot?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a pot. I have old cans.",vignette_start:"Your neighbor is a passionate gardener. She is now repotting and splitting her plants on the veranda, but since they grew so big she ran out of pots. Your roommate is also a crafty person, so they have different supplies stored in the basement. Your roommate has  ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour neighbor asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate answers the door and replies:",itemQuestion:"a pot",competitor:"old cans",sameCategory:"camping cookware",otherCategory:"ceramic plates",mostSimilar:"several pans"},{"":19,itemName:"pot-jam",settingName:"pot",question:"Do you have a pot?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a pot. I have camping cookware.",vignette_start:"Your neighbor has a beautiful apple tree in their garden. They harvested a lot of apples and are now in the middle of cooking apple jam in the garden. However, she ran out of space for cooking the apples since there are so many. In the basement, your roommate has ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour neighbor asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate answers the door and replies:",itemQuestion:"a pot",competitor:"camping cookware",sameCategory:"old cans",otherCategory:"ceramic plates",mostSimilar:"several pans"},{"":20,itemName:"towel-hair",settingName:"towel",question:"Do you have a towel?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a towel. There is a hair dryer.",vignette_start:"There is a Halloween party at your college dorm. Some of your friends who live in other dorms came over. A heavy rain started while they were on their way so now some of them want to dry their hair. In your dorm there is  ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour friends ask:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"a towel",competitor:"a hair dryer",sameCategory:"a dryer in the basement",otherCategory:"a blanket",mostSimilar:"paper towels"},{"":21,itemName:"towel-clothes",settingName:"towel",question:"Do you have a towel?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a towel. There is a dryer in the basement.",vignette_start:"There is a Halloween party at your college dorm. Some of your friends who live in other dorms came over. A heavy rain started while they were on their way so now some of them want to dry their costumes. In your dorm there is ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour friends ask:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your roommate replies:",itemQuestion:"a towel",competitor:"a dryer in the basement",sameCategory:"a hair dryer",otherCategory:"a blanket",mostSimilar:"paper towels"},{"":22,itemName:"candy-halloween",settingName:"candy",question:"Do we have any candy?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have candy. I have little trail mix packages.",vignette_start:"It’s Halloween. You just sat down to have dinner with your family as you hear the doorbell ring. Your partner answers the door and you hear that some kids are trick-or-treating. You have ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour partner wants to give them some sweets and calls back into the house:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your kid replies:",itemQuestion:"candy",competitor:"little trail mix packages",sameCategory:"ice cream",otherCategory:"soda",mostSimilar:"a big chocolate bar"},{"":23,itemName:"candy-dessert",settingName:"candy",question:"Do we have any candy?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have candy. I have ice cream.",vignette_start:"You just had lunch with your family and now your partner is craving some dessert. You have ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour partner asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Your kid replies:",itemQuestion:"candy",competitor:"ice cream",sameCategory:"little trail mix packages",otherCategory:"soda",mostSimilar:"a big chocolate bar"},{"":24,itemName:"bottle-plants",settingName:"bottle",question:"Do you have a bottle?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a bottle. I have a watering can.",vignette_start:"You and your colleagues like plants, so you decorated the window ledge of your office with several exemplars. The holiday season is about to begin at your company. Your colleague wants to water the plants before leaving. At your office there is ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour colleague asks:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"Another colleague replies:",itemQuestion:"a bottle",competitor:"a watering can",sameCategory:"a to-go mug",otherCategory:"a spoon",mostSimilar:"a glass"},{"":25,itemName:"bottle-water",settingName:"bottle",question:"Do you have a bottle?",competitor_response:"I'm sorry, I don't have a bottle. I have a to-go mug.",vignette_start:"You are about to go for a longer walk with some friends. It is a hot day outside. Someone forgot to bring a bottle of water. In your friend’s car trunk, there happens to be ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nThe person ask:",correct_response:"main",character_template:"The friend replies:",itemQuestion:"a bottle",competitor:"a to-go mug",sameCategory:"a watering can",otherCategory:"a spoon",mostSimilar:"a glass"}]},4984:function(e,t,a){"use strict";var o=a(5471),r=a(4302),n=a.n(r),i=a(6093),s=function(){var e=this,t=e._self._c;return t("Experiment",{attrs:{title:"answer-explanation-experiment"}},[t("InstructionScreen",{attrs:{title:"Welcome"}},[e._v(" Thank you for taking part in our experiment! "),t("br"),e._v(" You are participating in a study conducted by cognitive scientists at the University of Tübingen. Your participation in this research is voluntary. You may decline to answer any or all of the following questions. You may decline further participation, at any time, without adverse consequences. "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" Your anonymity is assured; the researchers who have requested your participation will not receive any personal information about you. "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" By pressing the button 'Next' you confirm that you are at least 18 years old and agree to participate in this study. ")]),t("InstructionScreen",{attrs:{title:"Instructions"}},[e._v(" Imagine you have met a curious alien Bo. Bo has learned English using a dictionary on its way to Earth, and is now trying to understand how humans communicate in real life. You take Bo on a walk through your neighborhood and explain to Bo how humans talk to each other. "),t("br"),e._v(" In the following, you will see short descriptions of everyday scenes that you and Bo observe on your walk. In each scene, one person asks a question. "),t("br"),e._v(" Your task is to teach Bo how to "),t("b",[e._v("understand when and how people ask questions")]),e._v(", so you explain to Bo "),t("b",[e._v("what possible goals the questioner might have in mind when asking the specific question")]),e._v(" they did in each scene. Please list at least three possible goals that the questioner might have in mind on each trial. "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" Notice that there will also be simple "),t("b",[e._v("attention checking")]),e._v(" trials. You will recognize them immediately when you read the important text on each trial carefully -- those trials contain instructions for you to type a certain word in the textbox. Please spell the words exactly as stated in the instructions. "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" Please respond naturally and reasonably. "),t("br"),e._v(" Please avoid jokes, insults or otherwise making the dialogues into something else than simple, harmless interactions with Bo. "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" Press 'Next' to start the experiment. ")]),e._l(e.trials,(function(a,o){return[a.type?[t("FreetypingScreen",{key:o,attrs:{trial:a,trial_type:"filler",index:o,progress:o/e.trials.length}})]:[t("FreetypingScreen",{key:o,attrs:{trial:a,trial_type:"main",index:o,progress:o/e.trials.length}})]]})),t("PostTestScreen"),t("SubmitResultsScreen")],2)},m=[],c=a(2543),l=a.n(c),p=a(9319),g=a.n(p),h=(a(3325),a(5514)),u=a.n(h),d=function(){var e=this,t=e._self._c;return t("Screen",{attrs:{progress:e.progress}},[t("Slide",[t("Record",{attrs:{data:{trialNr:e.index+1,itemName:e.trial.itemName,settingName:e.trial.settingName,trial_type:e.trial_type,correct_response:e.trial.correct_response,explanation:e.trial.answer,question:e.trial.question}}}),e._l(e.createScreen.split("\\n"),(function(a,o){return t("span",{key:o},[e._v(" "+e._s(a)),t("br")])})),t("br"),t("textarea",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.$magpie.measurements.answer1,expression:"$magpie.measurements.answer1"}],staticStyle:{width:"500px",height:"50px"},domProps:{value:e.$magpie.measurements.answer1},on:{input:function(t){t.target.composing||e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"answer1",t.target.value)}}}),e._v(" "),t("textarea",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.$magpie.measurements.answer2,expression:"$magpie.measurements.answer2"}],staticStyle:{width:"500px",height:"50px"},domProps:{value:e.$magpie.measurements.answer2},on:{input:function(t){t.target.composing||e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"answer2",t.target.value)}}}),e._v(" "),t("textarea",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.$magpie.measurements.answer3,expression:"$magpie.measurements.answer3"}],staticStyle:{width:"500px",height:"50px"},domProps:{value:e.$magpie.measurements.answer3},on:{input:function(t){t.target.composing||e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"answer3",t.target.value)}}}),e.$magpie.measurements.answer1&&e.$magpie.measurements.answer1.length>3&&e.$magpie.measurements.answer2&&e.$magpie.measurements.answer2.length>3&&e.$magpie.measurements.answer3&&e.$magpie.measurements.answer3.length>3?t("button",{on:{click:function(t){return e.$magpie.saveAndNextScreen()}}},[e._v(" Submit ")]):e._e()],2)],1)},_=[];function y(e){var t=l().shuffle(["competitor","sameCategory","otherCategory"]);console.log(t);var a=e.vignette_start,o=a.split(".").slice(0,-1).join("."),r=[o,e.vignette_continuation].join("."),n=e.vignette_continuation,i=e.question,s=e.character_template;console.log(e.correct_response);var m=t.map((t=>e[t]));m.splice(-1,1,"and ".concat(m.at(-1)));m=m.join(", ").concat(".");if("main"!=e.correct_response)var c=[a,m,n,'"'.concat(i).concat('"'),"\\n\\n"].join(" ");else{e.answer;var p=s.replace(" replies:","").toLowerCase();console.log(p);c=[r,'"'.concat(i).concat('"'),"\\n\\n","Please name at least three plausible goals that ",e.questioner," might have in mind when asking their question."].join(" ")}return c}var v={name:"FreeTypingScreen",props:{trial:{type:Object,required:!0},trial_type:{type:String,required:!0},index:{type:Number,required:!0},progress:{type:Number,default:void 0}},methods:{createText:y},computed:{createScreen(){return y(this.trial)}}},f=v,w=a(1656),b=(0,w.A)(f,d,_,!1,null,null,null),k=b.exports,N=l().sample(["odd","even"]);const x=4,T=1,C="odd"==N?g().filter(((e,t)=>t%2===0)):g().filter(((e,t)=>t%2!=0)),A=l().sampleSize(C,x);console.log(A);const I="odd"==N?u().filter(((e,t)=>t%2===0)):u().filter(((e,t)=>t%2!=0));document.onselectstart=()=>!1,document.oncontextmenu=()=>!1;var Y={name:"App",components:{FreetypingScreen:k},data(){return{trials:l().shuffle(l().concat(A,l().sampleSize(I,T)))}},computed:{_(){return l()}}},q=Y,z=(0,w.A)(q,s,m,!1,null,null,null),Q=z.exports,D={experimentId:"11",serverUrl:"https://magpie-cogsciprag.fly.dev",socketUrl:"wss://magpie-cogsciprag.fly.dev/socket",completionUrl:"https://app.prolific.com/submissions/complete?cc=CRQTR8R7",contactEmail:"polina.tsvilodub@uni-tuebingen.de",mode:"prolific",language:"en"};o["default"].config.productionTip=!1,o["default"].use(n(),{prefix:"Canvas"}),o["default"].use(i.Ay,D),new o["default"]({render:e=>e(Q)}).$mount("#app")}},t={};function a(o){var r=t[o];if(void 0!==r)return r.exports;var n=t[o]={id:o,loaded:!1,exports:{}};return e[o].call(n.exports,n,n.exports,a),n.loaded=!0,n.exports}a.m=e,function(){var e=[];a.O=function(t,o,r,n){if(!o){var i=1/0;for(l=0;l<e.length;l++){o=e[l][0],r=e[l][1],n=e[l][2];for(var s=!0,m=0;m<o.length;m++)(!1&n||i>=n)&&Object.keys(a.O).every((function(e){return a.O[e](o[m])}))?o.splice(m--,1):(s=!1,n<i&&(i=n));if(s){e.splice(l--,1);var c=r();void 0!==c&&(t=c)}}return t}n=n||0;for(var l=e.length;l>0&&e[l-1][2]>n;l--)e[l]=e[l-1];e[l]=[o,r,n]}}(),function(){a.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return a.d(t,{a:t}),t}}(),function(){a.d=function(e,t){for(var o in t)a.o(t,o)&&!a.o(e,o)&&Object.defineProperty(e,o,{enumerable:!0,get:t[o]})}}(),function(){a.f={},a.e=function(e){return Promise.all(Object.keys(a.f).reduce((function(t,o){return a.f[o](e,t),t}),[]))}}(),function(){a.u=function(e){return"js/"+e+".756ace6f.js"}}(),function(){a.miniCssF=function(e){}}(),function(){a.g=function(){if("object"===typeof globalThis)return globalThis;try{return this||new Function("return this")()}catch(e){if("object"===typeof window)return window}}()}(),function(){a.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)}}(),function(){var e={},t="qa_explanations:";a.l=function(o,r,n,i){if(e[o])e[o].push(r);else{var s,m;if(void 0!==n)for(var c=document.getElementsByTagName("script"),l=0;l<c.length;l++){var p=c[l];if(p.getAttribute("src")==o||p.getAttribute("data-webpack")==t+n){s=p;break}}s||(m=!0,s=document.createElement("script"),s.charset="utf-8",s.timeout=120,a.nc&&s.setAttribute("nonce",a.nc),s.setAttribute("data-webpack",t+n),s.src=o),e[o]=[r];var g=function(t,a){s.onerror=s.onload=null,clearTimeout(h);var r=e[o];if(delete e[o],s.parentNode&&s.parentNode.removeChild(s),r&&r.forEach((function(e){return e(a)})),t)return t(a)},h=setTimeout(g.bind(null,void 0,{type:"timeout",target:s}),12e4);s.onerror=g.bind(null,s.onerror),s.onload=g.bind(null,s.onload),m&&document.head.appendChild(s)}}}(),function(){a.r=function(e){"undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})}}(),function(){a.nmd=function(e){return e.paths=[],e.children||(e.children=[]),e}}(),function(){a.p="/goal-inferences/experiments/goal_sampling/"}(),function(){var e={524:0};a.f.j=function(t,o){var r=a.o(e,t)?e[t]:void 0;if(0!==r)if(r)o.push(r[2]);else{var n=new Promise((function(a,o){r=e[t]=[a,o]}));o.push(r[2]=n);var i=a.p+a.u(t),s=new Error,m=function(o){if(a.o(e,t)&&(r=e[t],0!==r&&(e[t]=void 0),r)){var n=o&&("load"===o.type?"missing":o.type),i=o&&o.target&&o.target.src;s.message="Loading chunk "+t+" failed.\n("+n+": "+i+")",s.name="ChunkLoadError",s.type=n,s.request=i,r[1](s)}};a.l(i,m,"chunk-"+t,t)}},a.O.j=function(t){return 0===e[t]};var t=function(t,o){var r,n,i=o[0],s=o[1],m=o[2],c=0;if(i.some((function(t){return 0!==e[t]}))){for(r in s)a.o(s,r)&&(a.m[r]=s[r]);if(m)var l=m(a)}for(t&&t(o);c<i.length;c++)n=i[c],a.o(e,n)&&e[n]&&e[n][0](),e[n]=0;return a.O(l)},o=self["webpackChunkqa_explanations"]=self["webpackChunkqa_explanations"]||[];o.forEach(t.bind(null,0)),o.push=t.bind(null,o.push.bind(o))}();var o=a.O(void 0,[504],(function(){return a(4984)}));o=a.O(o)})();
//# sourceMappingURL=app.d7b26a5b.js.map